（本片为真人真事片中事件发生于
1972年8月22日纽约布鲁克林）
主演：艾尔帕西诺
片名：热天午后
编剧：法兰克皮尔森
制片：马丁伯格曼、马丁艾尔芬
导演：薛尼卢梅
一定是总部来的
我们是可以处理
但是需要总部同意
我不知道
有很多人都碰过
苏菲雅，你可否帮我一下忙？
来了
打烊了，你想进来？
是的，先生
你是经理？
继续讲你的电话
我等下再回你电话
桑尼，我有不好的预感
你在说什么？
或许我们应该拿小一点的武器
你疯啦，枪都拿出来了
快去站在门边
站到门边去
全都不准动
全都不准动，快点
离警报器远点
靠中间站
他要是敢动就打烂他的头
用枪指着他
站中间点
桑尼
我没办法，桑尼
什么！
我下不了手，桑尼
你在讲什么？快指着他
我没办法，桑尼
我操！沙尔
-干嘛？
-你在哪儿？他办不到
去他的，叫他滚
快啊，桑尼
让他出去
-让他出去
-照着做，哈维
让他出去
对不起，桑尼
该死
-别把车开走
-那我怎么回家？
坐地铁，我们需要车
车钥匙给我
对不起，桑尼
把门锁上
他妈的
那边桌子底下有个女孩
他总算走了
现在可以办正事
听到了吗？
他刚跟我说什么？
谁躲在这里？
这是什么，松鼠吗？
喂
快点
你出来站到后面去
没人会伤害你的
快点
你站在后面去
把窗帘拉起来
到那边去
速战速决，快！
好
我们三十分钟内要完成
我只是要
遮住监视器
好了
你看
没录影也没警报器
你们拿了东西可以走人了吧？
-金库开了没？
-这我来处理
好，你来处理
等一下，你在做什么？
想启动警报器吗？用这把钥匙？
我一时忘了
听好
我是个天主教徒
我不想伤害任何人，懂吗？
-是的，先生
-不准按警报器
不准按警报器
少玩把戏
用另一把钥匙
玛莉安
把保险柜打开
把钱放进袋子里
怎样？
只有这些
你胡说什么？
下午已经有人把钱收走了
这里只剩一千一百元
-她说的是真的
-别杀我
我不敢相信
我真不敢相信
竟然会没有钱
-桑尼，快点拿钱
-我在拿了
怎么会这样？
好了，我们走
电话，你去接
沙尔，看好他
你跟我来
-坐下
-谁是这儿的领班？
是我
把这打开
不要全部拿
我在银行做过事
别以为我不知道警报器藏哪儿
别耍花招
你得这样做
先放进去再拿出来
一百块就到手了
我再回你电话
不行，这张是废物
因为有记号
这是狗屎
看？
高兴点
以后抢银行你就有经验了
银行会给你一打玫瑰花的
沙尔，叫经理接电话
嘿，经理
别打任何馊主意
我会叫
那边那个会咬
相信我，我是你们这一边
我们这边？鬼才信
我们这有年轻的少女
请注意你说话的字眼
我想说什么就说什么
注意用词？清光那抽屉
我不知道，你可能要问他
旅行支票
还有登记簿
登记簿
好了，走吧
这我来拿
沙尔，我们走吧
可恶
桑尼，你在干嘛？
我在烧登记簿
所有人往前走
我们要走了
把钥匙给我
哈维，把钥匙给他
我们不会伤害你的
我们要走了
桑尼，那是谁？
他是对面的保险业务员
大概是看到烟了
请把火扑灭
-我去拿水
-站着别动
-我待会儿回你电话
-打发他！
打发他！
别动歪脑筋
我来处理
-一切还好吧？
-没事，只是垃圾桶里的烟蒂
你们没事
-谢谢你帮我们留意
-哪里
-我们所有的钱都给你们了
-好吧，我们走
接电话，沙尔
带他们去金库
-钱呢？
-我拿了
他要跟我们一起走
拜托别关门，我们还要呼吸
等一下，等一下
-等一下
-什么事？
我撑不了的
我必须去厕所
这不是开玩笑的
我对幽闭恐惧症
好吧，还有谁要去？
-我也要去
-现在变成全都要去了
你可以检查看看
在你右手边的第一间
好吧，去吧
右手边的第一间
她是玛丽亚
我忘了她在这儿
这不是她的错，她常常这样
她只有十分钟休息
-常常忘记
-闭嘴，回去，全都不准去厕所
-回去，快点
-现在是银行抢劫
我是马维尼
爱讲话的
-这就充当你的马桶
-你的电话
什么？
电话是找你的
真的
-你在那里做什么？
-你是谁？
我是尤金摩瑞提探长
白痴，你们已经被包围了
不相信的话，看看窗外吧
我看到你了
-是谁？
-条子
把手放在头上走到前门
挂掉电话
快点
怎么会这样？
我有伤害你吗？
我对你不好吗？
-我的薪水不值得我当英雄
-这次抢劫你有没有计划？
还是你只是突然决定的？
你为什么要点火？
早就叫你们离开了
不听我的话
-他根本没有计划这次的行动
-我有计划！
只是我以为钱会被送来
而不是被收走
都是那个他妈的杰克
给的错误资讯
杰克又是谁啊？
幕后的策划人吗？
我们有难同当
我们必须离开这里
我需要时间思考
让我想想
仔细听好靠近这里一步
我就开始射杀人质一次一个，听到没？
你是谁？
有人叫珍妮吗？
谁是珍妮？
我就是
是你这松鼠，有没有先生？
他在电话上
接啊
我要说什么？
我不知道，随便你说啊
告诉他详情
真是他妈的闹剧
WNEW，热门音乐电台
听着，先别挂
-里面有人受伤吗？
-没有
反正不要靠近，不然我会开始
射杀人质一次一个，听到了吗？
别这么做等一下，让我跟你聊聊
里面有几个人？
别问了，你再打给我
你等下再打给我
他问你们几点会弄完？
什么？拜托你，小姐
快上
-后门在哪儿？
-里面锁住了
在哪儿？
走廊底的右边
沙尔，掩护他们
你随便煮嘛，什么都可以
好，我会的
我会的
-喂，该挂了
-亲爱的，我得挂了
我得挂了
我也爱你
现在待在这里面
我不知道发生什么事
可能有人不小心触动警报器
一定有办法逃出去的
放心好了
-你说的是真的吗？
-什么是真的？
你真的要
你真的要射杀人质？
-我只是放风声罢了
-我只想确认一下
因为我已经准备好了
是吗？好吧
-我是说真的
-我知道
所有人听着
我们现在出了点问题
但是别担心，很快就可以解决
只要跟我们合作
保持镇定，事情很快就解决了
听我们的话就不会有人受伤
首先，一步一步来
你要去厕所对吧？
她可以去
其他人也可以去
但我们要一起行动
保持镇静，他怎么了？
-他有气喘
-气喘？
我来处理
你叫什么名字？
-马维尼
-马维尼？
你跟我来
-他有气喘你们还要他当警卫？
-他上过警校
学怎么开枪吗？
他连枪都没有
他们早上升旗，一周可赚150元
我不知道他们学什么
我要把门挡起来
以免他们冲进来
过来帮我
等一下，等一下
先把这个拿走
你有小孩吗？
两个，我还想见到他们
别担心，你会的
你一直都还蛮听话的
我对你没有任何抱怨
没有抱怨
一点都没有
-你有没有银行保险？
-你知道我有
你好像蛮清楚银行的事
我还知道很多事
我只是想让你们安全离开
不是吗？
如果我要你跟我走？
如果你要带人的话
就选我吧
他们会开枪射你，你知道？
警察
他们根本不在乎银行什么保险
看看亚提卡
他们杀了42人
不管有罪无罪
总之放心
我不会选你的
我要选女人
结婚有小孩的
警察要是杀了她们
见报就不好看了
尤其是有小孩的
你还不错
你不会跟我玩把戏吧
调查局的人来了
你好吗，沙登？
你为什么不等他们出来呢？
我判断错误
我以为那些王八蛋看到警察
再听到已经被包围会吓破胆
而且
没人提及里面有人质
发生抢案了
记者是怎么突破封锁线的？
这次的银行抢案没有任何资讯
我是CBS的布莱恩
请问现场的状况如何？
我们在架设通讯设备
嫌犯在里面
我只能说那么多
有什么我会再跟你们说
你们在逃生梯那儿干嘛？
我是说屋顶
快上屋顶，可以吗？
-叫电信局了吗？
-全架设完毕
这支电话
能直接与银行里的人通话
-我是马维尼
-我是摩瑞提，让我跟他说话
-什么事？
-我是尤金摩瑞提探长
现在你们在里面
我们在外面，要怎么办
我不知道怎么办
首先，我想知道人质都安全吧
是的
-你自己一个人还是有同伙？
-我不是一个人
-还有沙尔
-沙尔？全名是沙尔瓦多？
沙尔是个杀手
我们参加过越战
杀人对我们来说小事一桩
-军队里？
-对
你叫什么名字？
你为什么要知道我的名字？
我想有个名字称呼你
只是给个名字不会怎样的
-叫我桑尼吧
-桑尼
听好，桑尼
-我想确认人质的安全
-嗯
然后我想要跟你商量
释放人质的事
等一下我会不带枪进去里面
你可以搜我身
取得你的信任之后
好
好的，那我该怎么相信你呢？
要公平嘛，对不对？
我可不想被枪扫射而死
-一些信号？
-没错，像什么？
放人质出来如何？
等一下
你以为我是他妈的白痴啊？
我才不会放我的护身符出去
-干嘛不跟我谈，你有话直说就好啦
-好吧，好吧
那你把女的放出来
不行，我这儿就只有女的
那就放其中一个
-你要一个干什么？
-公平交易啊
我不会带武器进去，但我总要知道
你不会把我当人质，是吗？
表示咱们互相信任嘛
-我要怎么跟你连络？
-拿起电话就可以跟我通话
拿起电话就可以跟我通话
他要一个人
-他，好吗？
-当然好
-可以吗？
-好
他出去
对方到底是何方神圣？
你一定要这样跟着我吗？
是的
他需要钥匙
你有吗？
-给他那一支就好，桑尼
-好啦
别开枪，别开枪
你们在干嘛？
他是人质耶，让他走
别开枪
我们决定让他先出来
-他是人质之一！
-放开他！
-你们怎么搞的
-他是人质之一
他是人质之一，放开他
你们这是干嘛？
我才不管！离远点！离开
别挡路
桑尼！等一下
桑尼！这就是你的不对
我们之间不是有电话吗？
我们有250个警察在外面
我们不知道，你在里面干什么！
你差点把他杀了，你疯啦！
-真聪明
-别落井下石，不是说全是女的？
干嘛又放一个男的出来？
你搞什么鬼啊！
-你不是要人质吗？我给你啦
-你要不要合作啊？
你要一个人质
我就给你一个，不是吗？
但你可以先用电话沟通嘛
出来吧，桑尼
我没有带任何武器
没带任何武器，来搜啊
你一看就知道了
-你要我出去做什么？
-来啊，我知道你想出来看看
-我要你知道你的对手是谁？
-我看得到你，为什么要出去？
你出来看啊
来嘛
好不好？
我这儿有沙尔顾着人质
如果我出事，他会知道的
我没忘记他，你就出来看嘛
出来嘛，好不好？
-我要先跟他说
-好吧，你不用带枪出来
桑尼，跟他说只有五分钟
别紧张
卡门，叫他们退后
他举白旗了
一切都还好
出来啊，桑尼
-他们太靠近了
-退后，妈的，你们在做什么？
-退后！退后！可以吗？
-叫他们退后
出来啊，你过来看看
来啊，你看
看上面那边
还有那边
还有那边，我们应有尽有
整个军队都出动了啊？
叫沙尔也出来看看吧！
看看我们有些什么
见好就收吧
-趁现在只是企图抢劫而已
-持枪抢劫
好啦，持枪抢劫
但没有人受伤
你把人质放了
不会被加上绑架的罪名
-最多判五年，但一年就可以假释了
-亲我
-什么？
当我被耍时，我需要有人亲我
-别这样嘛
-你是市内的警察吧？
抢银行是触犯了联邦法
他们会以绑架、持枪抢劫起诉我
我才不跟要想耍我的人讲话
叫负责人出来
-我就是
-我不要跟你这死肥猪谈判
-他在干嘛？
-退后！你们靠近干嘛？
-他们一直靠近是怎样！
-你们给我退后！退回去！
-回去！
-退回去！
-他很想尝尝杀我的滋味
-我们不杀任何人
-亚提卡
亚提卡
别忘了亚提卡事件！
你们说话跟放屁一样！
冷静点！
把枪放下
如果不是有记者
我们早就被杀光了
叫他们把枪放下！
他妈的，把枪放下
枪放下
把枪放下
亚提卡
就是这样！这样才对嘛
抢银行？
他为什么不跟我说他要钱？
他应该跟我说的
据了解，现在里面有8名人质
我们对里面的状况完全不清楚
除了被释放人质哈维卡文
所提供的描述以外外
你妈是个吸金女
干嘛还抢银行？
现在将镜头带到布鲁克林现场
班森小姐
请问里面情况如何？
能说什么？就是抢劫嘛！
他们在里面
-有共识了吗？
-叫沙尔的人
拿着枪，不太说话
你们相信摩瑞提探长吗？
他们不知道摩瑞提探长
我得走了
你抓我手干嘛？
她都出来了
-别进去
-大家都在里面，我要进去
-哈维还好吧？
-他没事了
-把电视打开
-女孩们
我被访问了
-讲好了！
-不错嘛！
-几乎所有人跟媒体都在外面
-是电视台
-干嘛？
-电视台记者想访问你
他们在外面
-什么事？
-桑尼，我们现正在实况转播
-你介意回答我们几个问题吗？
-不
你为什么要这么做？
-哈啰？
-你看
没事，我看到我自己了
你刚刚问
-我为什么要这么做？
-是的
-做什么？
-抢银行
我不懂你为什么问
-我抢银行是因为这里有钱
-你误会了
我是说你为什么想要抢钱？
你不能工作赚钱吗？
不行，要做什么？
你知道吗？你若要工作
就必须是工会的一员
没有工会卡，也没有工作
那不是工会的工作呢？
他搞不清楚状况啊？
什么叫不是工会的工作？
银行出纳员吗？
你知道他们一周赚多少吗？不多
起薪115元，对吧？
你要怎么过活？
我老婆和两个小孩要怎么活？
-你一周赚多少？
-我是来跟你谈有关
嗯，我在跟你说话
我们是娱乐，对吧
你有什么好处给我们？
你想要好处干嘛？
-你想拿钱？
-我不想，也不需要，你听着
我和我的同伴还有其他9个人
我们就快要死了
我们就要血溅五步，肝脑涂地
你会停播新闻，然后插播这个
给妇孺观众看吗？
-你可以给我什么？总得有些回馈
-桑尼
-你可以放弃
-放弃？
-你去过监狱没？
-没有
没有？那我们来谈
你他妈知道的事吧！
-你一周赚多少？
-很抱歉我们的通讯突然中断
-我们很快会再带您回现场
-喂？哈啰？
他妈的到底搞什么鬼？喂？
我想他们不喜欢你的用词
去他的，干
沙尔
他们很可能会跟我们谈判
外面那个人怎样我不清楚
如果我把调查局扯进来
他们说不定肯谈判
你觉得呢？
-沙尔？
-不行！
-你怎么了？
-你不是答应过我什么吗？
你是不是说
“不成功，便成仁”
-你是不是有说过？！
-我现在不是说那个
你要不要遵守诺言？
我们还做不做？
-当然
-那你又在说些什么东西？
我绝不回监狱
把他们全杀死，现在！
-用刺刀把他们全杀死！
-去你的
我们要架飞机，如何？
我们要架直升机
叫直升机开到屋顶上
再带我们去坐飞机
我们可以飞离这个国家
沙尔？
我们办得到！
沙尔，沙尔？
我们有王牌
我们根本不知道
我们有人质
我们从一开始就做错了
我们可以提出要求
他们一定会给我们要的东西
我要去热带国家
再也不用忍受下雪天
嘿，大嘴巴在哪里？
-你要不要一起去阿尔及利亚？
-阿尔及利亚？好啊
我们要去气候晴朗的地方！
沙尔，我办得到！
我已经撑了这么久
我办得到！
-帮我接摩瑞提
-探长
所有的人都去打电话吧
打个电话回家报备
我们要去旅行
-是的，桑尼？
-我有话跟你说
-我要出来
-非常好，我会在外面等你
走吧，他要出来了
现在，你要了解状况
一旦离开就不能回头
你知道我说什么吧？
不能回头！
想要跟谁说话
想要跟谁说再见的话，要快
没有
你有想去的国家吗？
怀俄明
那里不行，那不是个国家
没关系，我来处理
放下！听到没？
看，我什么也没带
这里也没有
要不要看我的袖子？
要不要看我的口袋？
你不敢不带枪吧？
摩瑞提
叫他们把枪放下
嘿，你！看不懂吗？
把枪放回枪袋去！
把枪放下！
懂吗？把枪放下！
那是什么？
谢谢！这就对了！
感激万分
你们终于开窍了
嘿，摩瑞提
都是你帮我的
犸利亚在里面
犸利亚！
他里面有枪！犸利亚
犸利亚，犸利亚
把他带走
-老天啊！
-怎么会这样？
-我有沙尔在里面
-别紧张，别紧张
通知管区警察
他是谁？
-只是个西班牙小孩
-犸利亚又是谁？
-她被你关
-沙尔要见桑尼，不然就要开枪了
-他是认真的，桑尼，他是认真的！
-沙尔
没关系，没关系
没事了
-对不起
-怎么发生的？
他女朋友是人质之一
你没事吧
他想杀我
-他打了你好几下
-我被打了好几下
让我看看你的头
-我在流血！
-让我看看
还好
你想跟我说什么？
刚有个人打电话来
一个疯子
打来说要杀死所有的人
每个人都想杀死所有的人
-这种人到处都会有的，对吧
-对啊
跟你说我有个提议
我想要一架直升机
还要可以带我去
任何国家的飞机
所以小的不行
要大的那一种
有酒吧和钢琴的那种
我很可能会离开国家
我不知道直升机是否能来这儿
-我帮你查查看吧
-可以停在屋顶上
不行，上面是柏油，停上去会垮的
让我打电话问我上司好吗？
-让我
-那干嘛不叫你上司来呢？
让我直接跟他们谈
就不必透过你了
-我们有时会意见不同
-对，所以我要跟他们说话
我会打电话问问他们怎么说
我和他们谈谈
还有其他的要求吗？
我要你把我太太带来这儿
-好，那你要给我们什么？
-你要什么？
女人质
老天啊，跟你说话真累
不是说过吗？里面全是女的
你到底要不要谈判啊？
你答应我一个要求
我给一个人质
你给我直升机，我给你一个人质
你给我飞机，我给你一个人质
你把我太太带来给你一个人质
其他的人用飞机送回家
我看他们能怎么做好吗？
在这段期间你赶快选人质
还有你太太在哪里？
我坐在这儿管我自己的事
我听到他们说桑尼抢劫银行
我真不敢相信
我抱起孩子就跑
我告诉你那个抢银行的人
绝对不是桑尼
桑尼绝不会伤害
或威胁任何人或东西
从我认识他到现在
他从没做过坏事
前天晚上
我们在康尼岛时
发现他买了一把有子弹的枪
我现才知道
他的行为有多么疯狂
都是受坏朋友的影响
我就看着他
到床上去
他像疯了似的一直骂小孩
然后他突然叫我带小孩去玩
我不想去
他就一直吼
乖，宝贝，嘘
一直吼个不停
在车里我问他
桑尼，你要那把枪干嘛？
不会是杀我
把尸体丢到河里吧？
我当时好害怕
我从不怕他的
他妈妈说我们一天到晚打架
还惊动警察
有一次我在车子里
想用千斤顶打他
却打到我自己
全身到处都是瘀伤
他却只穿上衣服戴帽子出门去
所以，我不相信是他做的
瓦基克小姐，听我说
你必须到银行来一趟
他的身体有可能会做
但是他的头脑绝不可能
亲爱的艾比我梦过掉到水里
无法接近水面
我呼吸困难
我惊醒后一身冷汗
一个朋友说我的问题是因为性压抑
犸格莉特，你还好吧？
你有没有对里面的女孩
做任何事？
又是他
这是谁？
桑尼犸格莉特
她怎么了？
这里没有空气
空调坏了吗？
苏，我很抱歉
-空调在哪儿？
-地下室
沙尔，我下去看看空调
-很快就回来
-桑尼！
干嘛？
我从没坐过飞机
又怎样？
我是说
坐飞机跟坐车一样
事实上，比车还安全
别害怕，沙尔
我要去检查空调了
沙尔，他们从后面进来了
进去金库，快点
-回去，退回去
-不，不要开枪
桑尼，注意点
带她进去，快进去
那枪是谁开的？
是谁开枪的？
快点，动作快！
好，抬腿
桑尼！
嘿，桑尼
拿扩音器给我！
桑尼！
你拿到扩音器了吗？
嘿，桑尼！
出来吧，桑尼！
桑尼！
干！这是我“最”需要的了
-桑尼！
-桑尼
你去处理一下吧！
桑尼，出来吧！
你们安静点儿行不行啊！
桑尼！
桑尼，出来吧！
桑尼？
桑尼！
-桑尼！
-王八蛋，你想害死那些人吗？
出来吧，桑尼！
桑尼，出来吧！
现在就出来吧！
快出来吧！桑尼
桑尼！
快出来吧，桑尼！
我可以看到你了，出来吧
来吧
你神经错乱啦？
-什么？
-你在里面开什么枪啊？
-我们有两百五十个警察在这边耶！
-我操！
-那你们在后头搞什么鬼？
-别再里头乱来！
你到底在玩什么把戏？
-什么？
-我们还要不要谈判？
-他们想进来是不是？
-谁？
少来这套！你心里明白
-这到底是怎么回事？
-你们这群蠢蛋
去后面看看发生什么事
-我真的不知道
-你别装模作样了
-通讯设备还没架好
-鬼扯
-找其他人来跟我谈吧
-去你妈的！
叫别人来吧
我不想再跟你谈了
-让我跟你谈吧？
-你这说一套做一套的人
-他们在后面做什么？
-我也不知道
-是吗？你不知道，又在装了
-那是突击队
他们喜欢开枪及攀岩走壁
没有你的下令
他们也可以蛮干吗？
是的！他们不听我的命令
我怎么知道
你们不会从屋顶上冲进来？
-因为我说不会！
-是吗？你说了很多，但全是放屁！
-我讲了什么？
-他们在干嘛？
-我不知道
-你不能回答我
-什么？
-我可以后面在干嘛！
-那告诉我他们在干嘛？
我们没有通讯设备
所以我派人到后面去
若沙尔开杀戒的话
全都是你的错，不是我的
-等等，你的要求我们都办好了
-是吗？
是的，我们找不到直升机
但是有辆巴士
飞机在肯尼迪机场待命
好吗？
可以吗？
好吧？
我们已经找到你太太
她现在正要赶过来这里
可以吗？
-你要去哪里？
-不去哪儿，我还是在这里
我以为我们要谈判的
我也是，但我们还没有谈
-我们现在谈
-你们却想从后门闯进来
你太太将在三十分钟内
赶到这儿
可以吗？
-满意吗？
-他们为什么枪还指着我？
把枪收好！
收好！
你也是
好了吧
-怎样？
-你还想怎样？
你是要我怎样？
我们什么都答应你了
你的要求我都答应
你还需要其他东西吗？
-有
-什么？
里面的人饿了
-可不可以给他们点食物？
-这没问题，要点什么？
-送些披萨进去，好不好？
-好啊！
嘿，卡麦
送些披萨进去
-可不可以再来点啤酒？
-嗯
不好不好，还是汽水吧？
好吧？
卡麦
记得还要有可乐汽水
-还要什么吗？
-再来点阿斯匹灵吧！
-还要阿斯匹灵
-有人不舒服
没有了吧？
-还有不准耍我！
-我不会的！我干嘛耍你？
我已经够烦的了
也不想自找麻烦
好吧！
没事了
直升机没办法停在这儿
沙尔，直升机没办法停在这儿
他们要换一辆大巴士
可容纳我们全部
接我们去机场
目前情况还不错
还有我刚帮你们叫了些吃的
也有阿斯匹灵
一切都进行得很顺利
对了！我还得付食物的钱
那些做记号的五元钞票在哪儿？
你刚做了件愚蠢的事
愚蠢的事？
我们还要继续这样下去？
对啊！不然你以为我在干嘛？
事情一直在进行
你以为这是件简单的事？
我不能激怒他们
还要顾到你们
我想点子又谈判
都是我一人在做
我在努力了
你想试试吗？
桑尼，你要的食物来了
我开始讨厌你了
跟着他进去，不会有事的
-多少钱？
-付过了，已经付过了
-没关系，我来付
-有零钱
拿去
零钱留着
你想要这个
你们喜欢？
摩瑞提，要不要？
还有很多
退后，该死的！
还要
可以帮我开门吗？
谢了
我成了明星！
踢
往上，翻转
抱她起来
她不会有事的
你踢得不错嘛！
踢！
往上！
就是在这里卡住的
她在愚弄自己
-谁有烟？
-我有
你不是不抽烟？
你不抽烟？
不抽
那你现在干嘛抽？
我快吓死了
你不抽烟吗？
-不抽
-为什么？
-我不想得癌症
-我的天啊！
把烟给我吧
爱抽就抽吧
我只觉得应该照顾自己的身体
我的身体？为什么？
身体是上帝的庙宇
你是认真的？
你可以抢银行
但不能沾恶习
是这样的吗？
你到底要不要抽？
要！
如果我因此得癌症
你得负一半的责任
不，那是因为你意志力薄弱
是的！我意志力薄弱
你的子弹呢？
我是马维尼
是摩瑞提
-喂
-你们千万不要轻举妄动
桑尼，你太太来了
-摩瑞提在哪儿？
-可能在酒吧里
在理发厅里
这是什么？
我们在你说的地址找到他
他说是他太太
在教堂结婚的
天啊！
礼昂！
礼昂！在这儿
礼昂
礼昂，我在这边
礼昂！
生日快乐！
-让让
-小心他的头
他是同志？
探长，他找你
我不要这保护罩，拿走！
要的时候都不会出现
他们不会开枪的
桑尼，什么事？
怎么了？他还好吧？
他只是有点头昏罢了
-让我跟他说话
-我等下叫他打电话给你
把门关上
安静点，我不想听到任何噪音
打字机！
挂电话！
快点！
给我些水！
礼昂
你还好吧，礼昂？
医院是不是帮你打针了？
我的天啊！
一针打下去我整个人都昏了
你可要振作点！
你待会儿还得劝他走出银行
我不知道
里面有八个人
还有个叫沙尔的人你认识他吗？
-不太认识
-他说他要杀死这八个人
我我我帮不上忙的
我不能阻止他
他不听你的听谁的？
我没办法跟他说
他不会听任何人的话
他整个夏天都怪怪的
六月的时候他就想杀我了
他用枪指着我的头
用刀割我
-还打我朋友
-你有试过叫警察吗？
有什么用？
他会更生气
他们阻止不了他的
-总得有人阻止他
-你不懂，他疯了！
他有老婆、小孩
是个好爸爸
他的妈妈
你该见识一下
看看他父母，他们简直是场大灾难
但他挑起重担
他探望他们，还帮他们付房租
难以置信
我是个想结婚的人，他不想
不过
但是他却结婚了
我不知道为什么！
你为什么想结婚？
我以为会对我有好处
可是
可是实际上没有
我以前很困惑
常常做傻事
比方说？
我在婚礼后
逃去大西洋城十天
桑尼气疯了
他知道我喝了酒
但是不知道我跟谁去了哪儿
我无法解释我所做过的事
后来我去看心理医生
他说
我是个
被困在男人身体的女人
所以，一听到消息
桑尼便想帮我凑钱做变性手术
但是他要去哪儿凑钱呢？
两千伍百元？
他本来就已经债台高筑了
他需要钱好让你做变性手术？
他为这件事非常烦恼
他因此常常无故发脾气
我也变得很沮丧
因为我知道
我永远不可能动手术
所以
我企图自杀
我吞下的药，数都数不清
蓝的、红的、黄的
所有的药我几乎都试过了
后来我被送进医院
桑尼来看我时
他看着我
问我
礼昂，为什么？
现在不是很好吗？
你不觉得
他是因为你才抢银行的？
嗯，我想是吧
难道你不想阻止他犯下大错？
我不敢跟他说话
礼昂，你脱不了关系
你是个共犯
-这件事不能怪我
-等等，你可以帮我们
我很怕
只要跟他说话
他在电话上又不能伤害你
我不能我不知道要说什么
跟他讲几句就行了
你考虑看看
他不想跟你说话
你什么意思？
我再去试试看
你不是已经在劝他了吗？
他不想跟我说话
警方现在正在询问礼昂谢摩
自认是双性恋的26岁男子
声称曾与嫌犯于11月
在教堂结过婚
根据我们在理发厅的消息来源指出
礼昂的婚礼
是由牧师柏克所主持的
礼昂的话已经过证实
7个男的伴娘
还有桑尼的妈妈和七十个客人
所有的同性恋团体都出席了
我们已经取得一张
礼昂穿婚纱礼服的照片
礼昂还透露
所有的礼服共花了七百多元
我们至今仍无法与该牧师连系
但据说他已被教会免职
全国各地的同性恋
已陆陆续续打电话进来
有人支持桑尼的行动
也有人谴责
认为这件抢案和这种婚姻
是“全然的表现欲”
我们正在报导
两名同性恋以人质做威胁
-要求坐直升机与飞机离开国家
-桑尼
桑尼电视上说
银行里有两个同性恋，你听到了没？
那又怎样？
他们爱怎么说就怎么说
随他们去说吧！
但我不是个同性恋
叫他们搞清楚
这会在电视上播出的
沙尔，你要我怎么做？
我管不了他们播出的内容
你要我怎么做
我已经尽全力了我管不了他们
沙尔
放心吧，他们像看戏很快就会忘的
无所谓
他们怎么说都无所谓
没事的
你怎么了？
你怎么可以让这小事坏兴致？
看开点
为什么飞机还不来？
不需要飞机时
它们总是从天上呼啸而过
你上飞机后
要跟驾驶员说什么？
这是应该知道的事情
荷兰其实是个不错的国家
-荷兰？怎么说？
-他们在战争时非常照顾难民
是个不错的民族
荷兰在哪儿？
荷兰在
在这儿！
可不可以给我地图？
快进金库，快点！
他们在等我们采取行动
桑尼
桑尼
快出来！
是他！就是他！
出来！我有话跟你说
-去吧！桑尼
-桑尼
桑尼！
桑尼！出来一下
桑尼？
出来一下
出来！
摩瑞提！
又怎么了？
把灯打开
摩瑞提！
你是谁？
调查局的沙登
很好
终于有人出面了
我们可以办正事了吧？
听好，把灯打开
还有空调
我们里面没有空调了
桑尼，我们不会给你面子了
给我面子？
你今晚都是在给我面子？
飞机准备好了
礼车半小时后就到
但是我要人质
少来，别唬我！
-我想跟你合作，而不是和你作对
-人质是我的护身符
什么时候放他们出来？
没有人告诉你吗？
我要听你亲口说
一辆车，换一个人质
一架飞机，换一个人质
到了机场，上了飞机
等我检查好
如果一切无误
我就会放了剩下的人质
-我要进去
-为什么？
确认大家都安全
他们很安全
我要亲眼目睹
你有种！
若我们杀了他们
还会让你活着出来吗？
我要亲眼看到
我得跟我同伴商量
沙尔，调查局的人要进来
你想杀我？
你一定很想杀了我
我不想杀你
但必要时我会的
这是你的工作，对吧？
我希望杀我的人
是因为恨我入骨
而不是因为工作因素
不要报上真名
他是调查局的人
只想确定各位小姐没有受伤
他们很久前就要了飞机
你们究竟在拖什么？
我们正在安排
两小时后就救你们出去
-两小时后？
-为什么不直接答应他们的要求？
他们会得到他们想要的
我们也要确定我们能得到我们要的
我要将你们平安带离这里
也包括你们俩
不要再靠近了
去告诉电视台
别再播银行里有两个同性恋
我会的，沙尔
桑尼，出来一下
你处理得很好
比一般人还好
减少可能会有的伤亡人数
你处理得很好
我尊敬你
把沙尔交给我们来处理
你只要不轻举妄动
就不会受伤
等一下，你在说什么？
你不必管
把沙尔交给我们处理吧！
你以为我会出卖他？去你妈的！
他说什么？
他只是告诉我他们的计划
我有告诉他电视的事，别担心
-就这样？
-对
那他为什么不在这儿说？
我不知道！
他想给我看车子要打哪儿进来
怎么了？
去倒杯水！
有没有手帕？
他们在披萨里下毒！
不是啦！
他有糖尿病！
他刚有喝可乐
别给他吃东西，我来拿
需要我们帮忙吗
马维尼先生？
这里有没有医生？
我们需要一个医生
-怎么了？
-经理有糖尿病
他不太舒服
我要搜身
只准他进来
桑尼
我已经说服礼昂跟你说话
他现在在电话上
他要接了
喂？
喂？礼昂？
喂？桑尼
怎么了？
你还好吧？
嗯，我出院了
我知道
我以为你永远也不能出院
-我没想过会是这样出院的
-是啊
你还好吧？
-我在发抖
-是吗？
摩瑞提说你不想跟我说话
我想可能是你吃药的关系
我刚还在想为什么你不想跟我说话
对啊，那里好糟糕
一进去他们就认定你疯了
然后就开始帮你打针
我的意思是
你一天到晚昏昏沉沉
病怎么好得起来？
我才刚刚开始清醒
-嗯
-你好吗？
-我很好
这个场面有点扯吧？
是啊
我不知道礼昂
我就快死在这儿了
我快死了
听听你自己说“快死了”的德性？
-你听听你自己！
-你在说什么？
你这话是什么意思？
什么你快死了
你知道你每天都跟我说
你快死了吗？
不是你快死了
是你在杀死你身边的人
礼昂，别这样好不好？
不要跟我废话
我想你可能不知道
这话是什么意思
是吗？我很清楚
你用枪指着别人的头
-我有时不知道自己在做什么
-对
很明显的你不知道
“睡吧，礼昂
这样我扣扳机时就不会痛”
你以为我在医院里做啥？
-我吃药是为了离开你，对吧？
-是啊
结果我现在又和你通电话
我没有工作，没有朋友
我必须要跟人接触才活得下去
对不起，你老是把死挂在嘴边
我听不下去了
我不知道我为什么
要在这忍受你这堆废话
你要我怎么回答？
事情已经发生了
-你居然说这种话
-对不起！
你知道我现在的处境
你应该知道我受的压力
我压力很大，你知道的！
你知道我的这些压力
你在医院里
全身插满了管子
又想动变性手术，对吧？
你跟我说了一堆废话
大家都给我气受
-每个人都要钱，你要，我就帮你凑
-对
可是我没叫你去抢银行啊
我知道你没要我去
我并不怪任何人
我不怪任何人
因为我是出于自愿的
你搞清楚了吗？
我只是想让你知道
我绝对能逃得出去
我会坐飞机离开这个地方
我只是想让你知道而已
我要你来这儿
只是想跟你说拜拜
或是你也可以跟我一起走
你可以自己决定
这就是我想讲的了
-我可以自己决定？
-对
我花了6个月时间试着离开你
现在却要我跟你一起离开？
你要去哪儿？
我还不知道
之前是说去阿尔及利亚
可能是去阿尔及利亚吧
为什么选阿尔及利亚？
我不知道
那里有一家强森饭店
-你疯了，知道吗？你真的疯了！
-我真的疯了！我知道
天啊！阿尔及利亚
他们带着面具走路
头上又有怪东西
-那边都是些疯子
-那我该怎么办？
-你可以选个好一点的地方
-哪儿？
瑞士还是丹麦？
对啊，那里不错
沙尔想去怀俄明州
天啊！我告诉他那不是个国家
他不知道怀俄明在哪儿
我和一个不知道怀俄明在哪儿的人
一起打劫，有问题的人不只你一个！
那么
沙尔跟你一起
喔我的天！
我看你们还是投降得好
我不会投降的
不然我何苦做这一切？
事情已经做到这个地步
现在何必投降？
我怎么能投降？
-你可以帮我个忙吗？
-什么忙？
带我来这里的人
他们认为我是同谋
怎么可能？太疯狂了
他们在唬你
想要耍你
-他们的确说我是共犯
-才不是
他们胡说八道，别相信
我一定得听他们的
我在监狱里会活不下去
-礼昂，你不可能会坐牢的
-你怎么知道？
我就是知道，你不会坐牢的
-拜托告诉他们
-拜托什么？
告诉他们什么？
告诉他们你我不是一伙的？
他们现在在听电话吗？
对
好极了！礼昂
真是好极了
你跟我通话，还让他们监听
你可真聪明
-我是被逼的
-什么意思？
你要我怎么办？
我身边有七万多个警察围着
-谁在听电话？
-不要怪在我头上
我没有怪你！
可是你知道他们在搞鬼吧？
讲什么我怪你
你一定知发生什么事
没错可是我
我只想知道谁在听电话？
摩瑞提？
摩瑞提，是你吗？
喂？
总有人说说话啊
他们还在听吗？
他们不会跟你说话的
好吧，他没参与这次的计划
他跟这件事一点关系都没有
可以了吧？
你们可以挂了吧？
他们挂了吗？
嗯
他们应该相信你了吧
这是他们要知道的，我帮你洗清罪名
谢谢你
你现在要怎么办？
我想
我想我会回去医院
他们人很好，也有心要帮我
你已经找到你要的东西了
我也不太确定
所以你还是会去动手术吧？
会呀，当然会
我还应该跟你说什么？
谢谢你
还有祝你一路顺风
-有缘再见面
-是啊
我会在梦里见到你的
我会写首歌的
-知道吗人生有时真有趣
-你说过很多次了
那拜拜了
-哈啰
-可不可以给我
你们把银行的电话全切断了
可不可以给我一支分线？
我要打电话给我老婆跟小孩
他要一支可以打出去的电话
给我接另一条线
好，我马上处理
你知道吗？
我可以打电话给任何人
教宗、太空人
智者中的智者
结果我居然得打给那个女人
我不知道该怎么办？
-喂？
-嘿，安琪
桑尼，天啊，我看到新闻了
-小孩在哪儿？
-他们还不知道我叫他们去邻居家
桑尼，我真的不敢相信
这不像你啊
我知道
你从来不会这样的
你从没伤害过任何人
你知道吗？我快死了
我快死在这里了
桑尼，我一直怪我自己
我知道你最近一直心神不宁
你前天像疯了似的骂小孩
还叫我去
坐小孩的云霄飞车
这太疯狂了，我不想去
你还骂我，逼我上去
我的心都碎了
整个人都崩溃了
你知道我的感受吗？
你当着这么多人骂我
因为你从来也没这样对我过
我以为你会杀了我
然后把尸体丢到河里
-安琪，闭嘴
-我是说我好怕你
-我怕死你了
-你给我闭嘴，听我说！听我说！
你看，又是这样
满口的脏话
我是想跟你说话，但你
我想我无法跟你说话！
你把我当成什么？
我是你老婆
你伤了我，你知道吗？
你伤透我了
你竟跑去与男人结婚？
我做错了什么？
我有拒绝过你吗？
我只不过肥了点
-不要说你自己胖，不要这么说
-你无法忍受我的肥胖
就像我无法忍受你抢劫银行
桑尼，这才是爱！
喔，你知道什么是爱？
既然你这么清楚
为什么不过来？
跟我谈爱
再说啊
桑尼，我好害怕
我好害怕
他们会不会枪毙我？
他们才不会枪毙你
你应该看电视的
他们有大炮、冲锋枪样样俱全
他们要抓的是我不是你
我好晚才知道你和沙尔出事了
我找不到保母，怎么去见你？
听着
我必须带他回去检查心脏
-他怎么了？会死吗？
-不是不是
只是要预防一下
这儿太暖了
好吧，带他出去
我不去，我还好
帮我打针就好
你干嘛啊？想逞英雄吗？
你看起来不太好还是出去吧
我不是逞强
我只想自己一个人，可以吗？
-没人吵你啊
-我希望你从没进来这间银行过
就这样
你不用假惺惺装好人
出柜上街头！
出柜上街头！
桑尼万岁！
女士们
请原谅我刚刚用的字眼
为什么？你刚说了什么？
-他说了什么？
-他骂脏话
-啊？
-他说什么？
他骂脏话
-操！
-我知道，玛莉安
我是基督教徒
不能听这些字眼
别这样嘛
-我们不要管他们了
-那就别管他们了
-怎么了？
-桑尼
桑尼，你可否出来一下？
是我妈
桑尼
有人来看你了，桑尼？
可否出来一下？
桑尼
桑尼，出来一下
你们看到那女人吗？
妈，你来干嘛？
-我不要你在这儿
-喔，桑尼
整个布鲁克林的人都在这儿
还有三家电视台来采访
-我知道怎么做，别担心
-我刚跟调查局的人谈过
-你跟谁谈过？不要跟任何人讲话
-他说
他说你要是现在出来
就会没事了
-我只是想帮你
-不要跟调查局的人说话
我全告诉他们了
包括你在越战的事
还有你以前工作表现一向很好
我还说你64年和高华德参加党大会
妈，听我说
我就要坐飞机去阿尔及利亚
-我会写信给你的
-阿尔及利亚？
-我必须离开这里
-真搞不懂你
如果我留在里跟你闲聊
他们就不会派车子载我们去机场
-他们会以为我要投降
-投降又会怎么样？
调查局的人什么都了解
他们知道不是你的错
他们知道
你是因为家里的压力大
-别把安琪扯进来
-我有说她的坏话吗？
-你的人生
-安琪没有错，是我错
本来你的人生是美好的
要不是安琪你也不会跟礼昂在一起
这你也知道
我不懂你为什么要跟她在一起
你有两个小孩在领福利金
-难不成你想跟她再生一个？
-妈，现在不是谈这个的时候
-妈，拜托
-你现在要怎么办？出来啊！出来
我不能出来，我不能
沙尔和人质都在里面
-要是我出来，沙尔会杀了他们的
-老天啊
-跑！跑！
-跑？
-跑！
-我能跑去哪儿？我不能跑
-或许或许我想应该
-我跑不了的，妈，拜托
妈，求求你回家，爸呢？
他没有来这儿吧？
没，他在生你气
他说他没有你这种儿子！
-他说你已经死了
-他是对的
我是个没用的边缘人
接近我的人都会倒霉
我必须要走了
麻烦带她回家，好吗？
带她回家
你知道你小时候有多可爱吗？
现在就回家去！
带她回去！
（十分钟）
我在身心
健全的状况下
你知道怎么写吧？
给我亲爱的太太
礼昂
我爱你
世界上
无人能比
直到永远
我留下了
两千七百元
是从我的寿险理赔金里拿出来的
就当做
你的变性手术费用
如果有剩
全都给你
在我的
我的一周年忌日
别忘了来看我
给我的老婆
亲爱的老婆
安琪
我理赔金中的五千元是要给你的
你是我唯一
爱过的女人
我在此令人鼻酸的一刻
重申对你的爱
给金咪
与提米
提米，希望你能记得我
你现在是这个家里的男人了
希望你能代我照顾这个家
我亲爱的妈妈
原谅我
你无法了解
我的言语
和行为
我就是我，我与众不同
我希望能有个军队仪式葬礼
我有权要求免费下葬
愿上帝保佑你
看顾你
直到我们再相会
我来签名
小心
小心
别这样嘛！探长
一张照片就好
退后！退后！
-你是司机？
-是的
我想检查一下
-这椅子可以拿下来？
-不行，固定住了
好吧！
灯从那边照过来
照那边
啊，你就是那个男的
我刚看到报导
你应该看看，你不会相信
我相信
但是席拉绝不会相信的
-谁是席拉？
-我妈
他们打电话来
叫我到公园西路258号
灯光照过来点
我以为又是一堆
从按摩院出来的客人
没问题了
我一定会记得你
这是墨飞探员，他来开车
不，我要他
-我要这个黑人
-我才不要蹚这浑水
别这样，没人会伤害你的
没有人会被杀
要杀早杀了，还等现在？
-我不答应
-你不答应？
你谁啊？
这里我下命令
我会付钱的
你要多少，一百元？
两百元？一千元？
怎样？
别看他，我才是老大
来嘛！
会很好玩喔
要杀杀白人，别杀我
你走吧
我要他
你以为你在跟白痴谈判啊？
滚，条子！
大家都想耍老千
我要所有人都到对面去
退到对面去
快呀
至少我知道我面对的人是谁
这支笔给你
站在这儿别动
桑尼，你的文件
-谢谢
-你必须签名
准备走了
我们要走了
沙尔，他在哪儿？沙尔
沙尔
就这样，我们要上路了
各位，要上路了
-我可以拿我的毛衣吗？
-拿你该拿的
沙尔
你还好吧？
-还好
-还好？
我们要上路了，好吗？
我们要上路了
沙尔，你看
注意看着他，他是司机
-我需要这把枪
-不，这是我的
你要看好这小子
现在怎么办？
等一下
好了，可以走了
转过来
手不要放开
等一下
数到三就放手
还不要放手
一
二
三，进车子里
我们成功了！
祝我们好运！
再见
我放了一人质了
跟着我的车
-帮我接肯尼迪机场
-沙尔
沙尔，我们成功了！
我们成功了！
按喇叭，我们走吧！
沙尔，帮个忙
把枪指别的地方
如果路上颠簸的话枪很可能会走火
你们好了吗？
我们要准备离开这儿
一路上不准有任何的麻烦
路口都安排好了？
好我们现在就要出发
10—4
会没事的
沙尔，你一定要记得要把枪口向上
他在那里干嘛？
他在安排事情
就是这架？没错！
沙尔，看到没？就是那架飞机
糟糕
我忘了问上面有没有吃的
上面会有食物吗？
看，那就是你要求的飞机
-人质呢？我们约定好的
-对
-好，谁要走？
-苏菲雅？
玛莉亚！
我会帮你们祷告的
沙尔
第一次坐飞机
不要太害怕
我刚才想起我一整天都没吃
飞机上会有食物吗？
飞机上有汉堡，准备好了吗？
-沙尔
-怎样？
要走了喔
好啊
好，我们走吧
沙尔
我们不想这时候出意外
记得把枪口朝上
-你要第一个出来吗？
-我准备好了
别射我
手脚张开
我们已处理完了
墨飞会在车子里报告
你来报告
把枪收起来
退后
起来，桑尼
你被逮捕了
你有权保持沉默
你有权请律师为你辩护
你所说的任何话
都会做为呈堂证供
若你无法负担律师费用
政府会在审问前
指派你的辩护律师
沙登探长
可否麻烦你待在这儿
直到所有人质
都进入航站大厦为止？
重复
沙登探长
可否麻烦你待在这儿
直到所有人质
都进入航站大厦为止？
是，我收到了
我们会守在这儿
（桑尼瓦基克在联邦监狱里服刑二十年）
（安琪瓦基克和她的小孩靠领福利金生活）
（礼昂谢摩现在已经变为女人住在纽约市）
It has to be from downtown.
It's handled through this office,
but it requires downtown approval.
I don't know.
It has been submitted.
Sylvia, can you help me with this?
Coming.
Closing time. Going in?
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
I couldn't say.
-You the manager?
-It's a matter of policy.
It-- It looks--
Keep talking like nothing was wrong.
Listen, let me call you back.
Sonny, I'm getting really bad vibes.
What are you talking about?
Maybe we should take
something smaller, Sonny.
You crazy? He started already.
He's got the gun out.
Go on, go over by the door.
Get over by the door.
Freeze!
-Nobody move.
-Get over there!
Okay. All right,
get away from those alarms.
Come on, get in the center.
He moves, take his head off.
Put the gun on him !
Get out of the center.
Sonny.
I can't do it, Sonny.
-What?
-I'm not gonna make it.
-What? Put it on him.
-I can't do it, Sonny.
Oh, fuck me. Sal.
-What?
-Where are you? He can't make it.
Fuck him. Let him go!
Come on, Sonny!
All right, let him out.
-Let him out!
-Do what the gentleman says, Howard.
Let him out!
I'm sorry, Sonny.
Oh, shit.
-Stevie, don't take the car.
-How do I get home?
Take the subway. We need the car.
Stevie, the keys.
-I'm sorry, Sonny.
-Right.
All right, lock it.
Shit.
-What do you want?
-Sonny, there's a girl under that desk.
All right, go.
We got rid of him.
So now we just move it along.
-Sal, you got them?
-I got them.
Okay. What'd he say to me?
Wait a minute.
Anybody here?
What's this, a squirrel?
Hey, you. Come on. Go ahead.
In the back there.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Go ahead, get to the back.
-Pull the drapes!
-Howard.
Now, you, to the back there.
Go to him, right there.
Okay. We're gonna move this now.
Just moving along.
Come on. Gotcha. Gotcha.
We're moving right along, folks. Gonna
get this thing done in half an hour.
We just gotta block. . . .
Oh, shit.
Here.
Knock out the TV.
There we go.
See? No replay, folks.
No alarms.
Let's get you all fixed up
and on your way.
-Right. Is the vault open?
-I can take care of that.
That's good. Let's go.
Take care of it.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are you trying to do?
Trip the alarm?
Use the spot key?
-I must've been out of my mind.
-You get your mind right!
I'm a Catholic. I don't wanna
hurt anybody, understand?
-Yes, sir.
-No alarms.
-No alarms!
-Okay.
No games, all right?
Use the other one.
Miriam. . .
. . .open the safe.
It's all right. It's all right.
Here. Put it in this.
What?
That's all there is.
What are you talking about?
They picked it up today.
There's only $1 1 00.
-It's true.
-He's gonna shoot me.
I can't believe it.
There's no money here.
-Come on, Sonny, let's do it!
-I'm doing it!
Too much. This is too much.
This is too much.
All right, come on. Let's go.
Somebody-- You answer it.
Watch him, Sal. You, come with me.
Watch him.
-Sit down.
-Who's the head teller here?
-I am.
-Come here.
All right, open it up.
Nope, not all of it.
Look, I worked in a bank.
I know the alarms. All right?
Don't play games with me. See.
You take one of these,
go like this. . .
. . . in here, and out it comes.
You got your 1 00.
I'll call you back.
No, it's decoy money.
It's marked.
It's shit.
See?
Cheer up, you'll be
the veterans of a robbery.
You know the bank
sends you a dozen red roses?
Sal, let him answer it.
Hey, you. Manager. Fucker!
Don't get ideas.
I bark, that man there, he bites.
-Believe me, I'm on your side.
-On my side, shit.
Listen, we got young girls here.
You could watch your language.
I speak what I feel.
"Watch my language."
Empty the drawer out.
I don't know.
You'd have to find out from him.
Traveler's checks. . .
. . .and the register.
The register.
You've got it.
All right, let's go.
I'll take that from you.
All right, Sal, here we go.
Shit.
Come on.
-Shit.
-Sonny, what the hell are you doing?
I'm burning the register here.
Moving right along, folks.
All right. Okay.
We're leaving.
Let me have the keys.
Howard, give him the keys.
-Come on.
-Howard.
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
We're gonna leave.
Sonny. Who's that?
It's the insurance guy from across
the street. He probably saw the smoke.
Please, put out the fire.
-I'll get some water.
-Stay right there!
No, no, please, don't--! Don't do it!
-I'll call you back later.
-Get rid of him.
-Come on, get rid of him !
-Howard.
Howard.
-Use your head.
-I can handle it.
-Everything's all right?
-Cigarette butt got in the wastebasket.
-Well, then you're okay.
-Yeah. Thanks for keeping an eye out.
Okay.
-Good.
-Go now. We gave you all we've got.
Okay, we're going.
Answer the phone.
Sal, get them in the vault.
Come on, in the vault.
-Where's the money?
-I'm getting it. Got it.
He's gonna come with us. Okay.
No, please don't close that door.
How can we breathe?
-I can't explain. I'll call--
-Right.
Wait a minute.
-Wait a minute. Listen.
-What?
I'll never make this.
I'll have to go to the toilet.
Honey, it's no joke.
I got a terrible fear
of being locked in.
-Who has to go to the bathroom?
-I do too.
-See, now they all wanna go.
-Look, do you wanna check it out?
It's the first door on your right.
All right, Mouth, let's go.
First door on my right.
It's Maria!
Listen, I-- I forgot she's in there.
It's not her fault.
She's always pulling this.
She's supposed to have 1 0 minutes. . .
-. . .she takes 1 5--
-Shut up! Nobody goes to the bathroom.
-Let's go, out.
-We're having a bank robbery.
Mulvaney speaking.
All right, Mouth. Mouth.
-Here's your toilet.
-It's for you.
-What?
-Telephone call.
For you.
Yeah.
-What are you doing in there?
-Who's this?
Detective Sergeant Eugene Moretti,
asshoIe. We got you by the baIIs.
I'm Iooking you right in the eye.
Right now I can see you.
-Who is it?
-Cops.
You come to the front door. . . .
Hang it up.
Get on the side of the street.
Come on, let's go.
How'd that happen?
Did I do anything to hurt you?
Did I treat you badly?
-Look at my salary. I won't be a hero.
-Did you have a plan or what?
What did you do,
just barge in on a whim?
-Why'd you have to light a fire?
-I told you to get out. . .
. . .when you could,
but you had to hang around.
He don't have a plan.
It's all a whim.
-Rob a bank, right?
-I had it planned !
Only the money should have
been delivered, not taken away.
That fucking Jack, downtown, he gave
me the wrong information. That fuck!
What is this Jack supposed to be?
A mastermind or what?
I wouldn't be arguing with me.
We're all in a barrel together
and we wanna get out of it.
All right, I gotta have time to think.
I gotta think.
Oh, shit.
Listen, bastards. You keep away,
or we'll start throwing bodies out. . .
. . .one at a time. Got that?
Who is this?
There a Jenny here?
-Who's Jenny here?
-That's me.
It's the squirrel.
You got a husband?
Yeah? Well, he's on the phone.
Go ahead.
Well, what could I tell him?
I don't know, tell him whatever.
Tell him the truth.
What a fucking comedy.
W-N-E-W, plays all the hits.
Listen. Now, don't hang up.
-First off, is anybody hurt in there?
-No.
Keep away, or we'll start throwing
bodies out, one at a time. You got that?
Don't do that. Let me talk to you for
a while. How many people you got?
No, call me back.
-Call me back.
-Excuse me.
He said he wants to know
what time you'll be through.
What? Oh, girlie, please.
Come on. Let's go.
-Where's the back door?
-It's locked on the inside.
Where is it?
Through the passageway to the right.
Sal, cover them, cover them.
You could just go ahead
and cook whatever's there.
Ready for riot gang.
3-4, sergeant.
3-4, sergeant. Is that roof--?
-Negative.
-TeII units preset.
Oh, yes, I will. Yes, I will.
-Let's go, come on.
-Honey, I've gotta go now.
I gotta go.
I love you too.
All right, inside here.
Sal, I don't know what happened.
Maybe somebody tripped an alarm
or something. I don't know.
-But there's a way out of this.
-Listen.
-Were you serious about what you said?
-About what?
About throwing--
About throwing those bodies
out the door?
-That's what I want him to think.
-I wanna know what you think.
Because I'll tell you right now,
I'm ready to do it.
Right. Okay.
-I mean it. I mean it.
-I know.
All right.
Listen, everybody.
I know we got a problem here, right?
But there's a way out of this thing.
I'm telling you.
All you gotta do is cooperate with me.
Stay cool, and we'll get out of this,
all right?
Nobody gets hurt if you listen to me.
First, we'll do things a step at a time.
You gotta go to the bathroom, right?
She'll get to go to the bathroom.
Everybody who has to go
will get to go to the bathroom.
We'll do things together.
Now, stay cool--
What's the matter with him?
He's got asthma.
-Asthma?
-Yeah, asthma.
Asthma. Shit.
All right, I'll take care of that.
-You, what's your name?
-Mulvaney.
Mulvaney? Come with me.
-He's got asthma and he's a guard?
-They go to guard school.
To learn what, how to shoot?
He doesn't have a gun.
They earn a $1 05 a week
to fold the flag in the morning. . .
. . .straighten up.
I don't know what they learn.
All right, I wanna block that door. In
case they try coming in, I can hear it.
All right. Let's move this.
Wait a minute. Hold it, hold it.
Let's get rid of this.
You got kids?
I got two kids and I'd like
to see them again.
You'll see them again.
You're being cooperative with me.
I got no complaints
against you, whatsoever.
Whatsoever.
You got bank insurance?
You know I do. You seem
to know a lot about bank procedure.
I know a lot about a lot of things.
I just wanna get you
out of here safe, right?
What if I take you with me?
If you take anybody. . .
. . . please take me.
They'll shoot you, you know?
The cops. . .
. . .don't care about bank insurance.
See what they did in Attica?
Forty-two people, they killed.
The innocent with the guilty.
Anyway. . . .
I won't take you. I'll take one of
them girls, a married one with kids.
Cops don't like it in the papers when
they shoot a married woman with kids.
You're all right.
You won't fuck with me, will you?
Come on, set a car.
-Help with those barricades.
-Move them back.
There's the FBI.
How you doing, Sheldon?
Why didn't you wait
and try to take them outside?
I made an error in judgment.
Thought the S.O. B.s would be
remorseful at the sight of a policeman.
And you know something?
Nobody said "hostage" yet, understand?
-We have a bank robbery here.
-Yeah.
How did the press guys
get through the barrier?
We don't know what's up yet.
We're setting up communications.
This is Ron Cummins from CBS.
Can you tell me the situation?
We got the-- We're setting up
communications now.
The perpetrators are in the bank.
That's all I can say now.
When I get it, you'll get it.
That's all. Okay.
What are you doing
on the fire escape?
I said on the roof.
Now, get up on the roof, will you?
-Get the phone company?
-It's being set up now.
This phone is gonna be
a direct line into the bank.
-Mulvaney speaking.
-Moretti here. Let me talk to him.
-Yeah.
-Detective Sergeant Eugene Moretti.
-Okay. . .
. . .you're in there, we're out here.
What do we do?
-I don't know. What do we do?
-Listen.
-Are the people in the bank okay?
-They're okay.
-You aIone or you got confederates?
-I'm not alone.
-I got Sal.
-Sal, what's that for, Salvatore?
Yeah. Sal, he's a killer.
We're Vietnam veterans
so killing don't mean anything to us.
-In the Army?
-In the Army, yeah.
-So there's you, what's your name?
-Why do you wanna know my name?
Give me any name.
Just so I got something to call you.
Let's be reasonable, okay?
Just give me your name.
Call me Sonny.
-Sonny?
-Yeah.
Okay. Now listen, Sonny.
I wanna see
if the people are okay.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Then I wanna work out a way
to get them out of there.
I wanna come over without a gun.
You can frisk me so you can trust me.
We'll find a way out of this.
Right.
I just wanna find some way
that I can trust you too.
Not be on the street
where you could just shoot me.
-Some sign, right?
-Right. Like what?
How about letting the people out?
Come on, now. Who do you think you're
dealing with? A fucking idiot here?
They're keeping me alive.
I'm gonna let them out?
Talk to me. Just talk to me straight.
I'm ready to talk.
Okay, okay.
How about giving us the women?
No, I've got women.
That's all I've got here.
Okay. Give me something.
Give me one of them.
-Why do you want one?
-It's Iike a fair exchange.
-I'll come over. I won't pack nothing.
-Yeah?
I don't know if you'll take me hostage.
It's a sign of trust.
-How do I call you back?
-We got a direct Iine here.
Pick up the receiver and I'm here.
He wants one.
-Him, right?
-Right.
-Right?
-Okay? He goes.
-Okay.
Can you get up?
What are we dealing with here?
Hey, you have to keep
checking me out all the time?
Yeah.
-Here you are. Your stomach okay?
-It's all right.
He'll need the keys.
Got the keys?
-Just the one, Sonny!
-Right.
-Hey, don't fire! Don't fire!
-What are you doing?
-Get away from him !
-That's a hostage!
-Don't fire, don't fire. HoId your fire.
-Hold your fire!
We voted to send him out!
-He's one of the hostages!
-Get away from him !
-What's the matter with you?
-He's a hostage!
He's one of the hostages.
What the hell's the matter with you?
I don't give a fuck, goddamn it!
Get away. Get out of here.
Hey, Sonny! Wait a minute, Sonny.
That was your fault, Sonny.
You know we had
the communications set up here.
We're not set up properly.
We've got 250 cops here.
We don't know
what's going on in there.
-You almost killed him ! Are you crazy?
-That was smart.
You say you got nothing but women,
and throw out a guy. What's going on?
You wanted a hostage,
I gave you one.
-You gonna deal with us or not?
-I gave you one.
You did, but you should have picked up
the phone. Come on out.
Look. I ain't packing nothing, see?
I ain't packing nothing.
You can come out and frisk me.
You can tell.
-Why you want me to come out?
-To look at something.
-To see what you're up against.
-I can see it. Why come out?
Come out and see it all, all right?
Come on.
All right?
Sal is in there with the other people.
Anything happens to me, they'll get it.
I don't forget about Sal.
Come out and look. Okay?
Come on. Okay?
-I gotta check with him first.
-All right. You don't need that artillery.
Sonny, five minutes.
You tell him that.
Take it easy.
Get them back.
He's got a white flag.
All right. Okay.
Everything's all right.
-See that?
-Right, yeah. Okay.
-Come on out, Sonny.
-He's too close here.
Get back!
What the fuck are you doing?
-Get them back.
-Get back!
-All right.
-Okay. Come on out.
Take a look at this. Come on.
Here, look. Look up here. Look.
Look.
Look over here, huh?
Over there, right?
We got everything here, okay?
You got the militia out here, huh?
Let Sal come look.
What hope have you got?
Come on. Quit while you're ahead.
-It's only attempted robbery.
-Armed robbery.
All right, armed, then.
Nobody's been hurt.
Release the hostages. No one
will worry over kidnapping charges.
The most you'll get is 5 years.
-You'll get out in one year.
-Kiss me.
-What?
When I'm being fucked,
I like to get kissed on the mouth.
You're a city cop, right?
Bank robbery's a federal offense.
They got me on kidnapping, armed
robbery. They're gonna bury me.
I won't talk to somebody
trying to con me.
-Get someone in charge.
-I am in charge.
I won't talk to some flunky pig
trying to con me. What's he doing?
-Get back!
-Why are they moving in?
Will you get the fuck back there?
Get back there. Get over there!
-Go on back there, man !
-Get over there!
He wants to kill me so bad,
he can taste it.
-No one's gonna kill anybody.
-Attica! Attica! Attica!
Attica! Attica! Attica!
Attica! Attica!
Attica!
Attica! Remember Attica!
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Your word don't fucking matter!
Come on, calm down.
--to put their guns down !
Put your guns down !
Wasn't for the TV guys,
they'd kill us all.
Tell them to put their guns down !
Get back!
-Put those guns down !
-Put the guns down !
Get back!
Put those fucking guns down !
Put those guns down !
Put them down ! Put them down !
Put those fucking guns down.
Put those guns down.
Attica! Attica!
You got it, man !
You got it! You got it!
You got it, man ! You got it, right?
You got it, right?
You got it. You got it.
--headquarters in Washington--
-Robbing a bank?
-What was--? What?
--as to the identity of one of the men.
Why didn't he tell me
he needed money?
He should've come to me
if he needed money.
I can't believe it.
We know that 8 peopIe
are stiII being heId in the bank.
The situation inside the bank
is totaIIy unknown to us other than...
...descriptions that have been
obtained from Howard Calvin.
Why steal when your mom's a sucker?
We'll switch you now to Ron Cummins
at the bank in Brooklyn.
Miss Benson, what's it like inside?
They're holding up,
what can you say?
-The guy with the gun on us. . .
-Got a deal?
-. . . he's a quiet type.
-Any confidence in Detective Moretti?
They don't know Detective Moretti yet.
I gotta go now.
What's this with the hands?
She's out, let her stay out.
They're my girls.
I'm going back in there.
-Howard, how is he?
-Howard's all right.
-Put the TV on.
-Girls, I was interviewed.
Sal, looks good.
Everybody's out there.
They got the whole media.
Television people. Television people. . .
. . .they wanna talk to you.
They're out there.
Yeah?
Hello, Sonny.
Sonny, you're on the air.
-WouId you answer a few questions?
-Yeah.
Why are you doing this?
-Hello?
-See, now. . .
. . . I just saw myself there.
What'd you--?
-Why am I doing it?
-Yes.
-Doing what?
-Robbing a bank.
What? I don't know
what you mean by that.
I'm robbing a bank
because they got money here.
I mean, why do you feel
you have to steal for money?
Couldn't you get a job?
No. Doing what?
You know-- You know, if you want a
job, you gotta be a member of a union.
See. If you got no union card,
you don't get a job.
What about non-union jobs?
What's wrong with this guy?
What do you mean, non-union?
Like what, a bank teller?
-Know how much a bank teller makes?
-Not much.
Not much. $1 1 5 to start, right?
You gonna live on that?
I got a wife and kids. How am I gonna
live on that? What do you make a week?
-I'm here to taIk to you, Sonny.
-No, well, I'm-- I'm talking to you.
We're entertainment, right?
What do you--? What do you got for us?
What do you want to get for it?
-Do you expect to be paid?
-I don't need to be paid. Look.
I'm here with my partner and nine
other people, see, and we're dying.
You're gonna see our brains on the
sidewalk. They'll spill our guts out.
Gonna show that on television?
Have housewives see that?
Instead of As The World Turns?
What do you got for me?
I want something for that.
-Sonny.
-Yeah.
-You couId give up.
-Give up?
-Right. You ever been in prison?
-No.
No. Let's talk about something
you fucking know about, okay?
-How much you make a week?
-Transmission has been interrupted.
PIease stand by, we wiII return
to our speciaI newscast very soon.
Hello? What the fuck happened?
Guess he didn't appreciate
your language.
Fuck him.
Sal.
I don't know,
they might deal with us.
You know? I mean, I don't know about
that guy out there.
But if I get the FBI involved in this,
they might deal.
What do you think?
No.
-Sal. . . .
-No!
-What's the matter with you?
-You made a promise, didn't you?
-Did you promise me something?
-Yeah.
Did you say either we get away clean
or we kill ourselves?
-Did you?
-I'm not talking about that.
-You believe in keeping your promises?
-Yeah.
-Then does it still go?
-Well, what are you talking about?
-I'm trying to--
I ain't going back
to that prison, Sonny.
-Yeah.
-Kill them all. Now.
-Take your bayonet, jam it into their--
-Fuck you, you fucker.
Shit.
We ask for a jet.
What do you think?
We get a helicopter.
We get a helicopter here,
it lands on the roof. . .
. . .and takes us to a jet.
And we fly the fuck out of the country.
Sal. Sal. . .
. . .we can do it.
Sal. Sal, look.
We got them. We don't even know it.
We got the hostages.
We've been looking at this the
wrong way. We make the demands.
They're gonna give us
anything we want.
I'm flying to the tropics.
Fuck the snow.
Hey, where's the Mouth?
-You ready to go to Algeria?
-Algeria? Yeah, sure.
We're all going to sunny climes!
Sal, I can make it happen !
I can make it happen !
I made it happen so far, right?
I can make it happen.
-Yeah.
-Give me Moretti.
Sarge.
All of you, go ahead, make phone calls.
Call home or whatever.
We're all going on a trip.
-Yeah, Sonny.
-Yeah. I wanna talk to you.
-And I'm coming out.
-Good, I'll be there.
Let's go. Come on, he's coming out.
Sal.
Now, you gotta understand something.
If we leave the country,
there's no coming back here.
There's no coming back.
If there's anyone you wanna talk to. . .
. . .you wanna say goodbye to,
do it now.
No.
Is there any special country
you wanna go to?
Wyoming.
No, Wyoming. . . .
That's not a country.
That's all right.
I'll take care of it.
All right, put them down !
Put them down. You need a gun?
What do I have?
See this here, look.
I got nothing up my sleeve.
I got nothing here either.
Wanna see my pockets? Here.
You need that gun, right? Yeah.
Moretti, tell them
to put their guns down !
Hey, you, see that?
Put it in your holster.
Put the guns down !
You know what it means
to put a gun down? What's this?
-What's this?
-Put them down.
Right. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You got it, right?
You got it, baby! Hey, Moretti !
You ready to let these--?
You got Maria in there!
Maria!
He's got a gun in there! Maria!
Maria! Maria!
Get him the fuck out of here!
How the hell did that happen?
-I got Sal in there!
-Take it easy.
-Notify the precinct, all right?
-Who the fuck is that?
No, no, no.
He's one of them Spanish kids.
-Who's Maria?
-She's inside.
Sal wants to see Sonny,
says he'll shoot unless he does.
-Sal. Sal.
-He's serious. Sonny, he means it!
-He means it.
-It's all right. It's all right.
It's all right.
-Hey, man, I'm sorry.
-How'd that happen?
You got his girlfriend.
You know the Spanish. You okay?
That fuck tried to kill me.
-You look all squeezed out.
-Squeezed out, I'm squeezed out.
Yeah, yeah. Okay. Wait, let me see.
Let me see your head.
-I'm bleeding.
-Let me see it.
Let me see it.
Oh, Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
It's all right. You want to
talk to me about something?
You should've heard that phone call.
Calls up, some creep,
says, "Kill everybody."
Everybody wants to kill everybody.
You're gonna get assholes like that
anyhow, right?
Right.
Yeah, I wanna talk to you.
I got an offer.
I want a helicopter out of here.
And a jet to go wherever I wanna go.
So I don't want a little jet,
I want a big one.
One with a bar, a piano.
Maybe I wanna go out of the country.
I don't know, Sonny. I don't know
whether a helicopter'll fit in here or not.
I'll check it out.
-It could land on the roof.
-No, that's asphalt.
You know what'll happen,
it'll break through.
I'll call my superiors, you understand?
Why don't you
bring your superiors here?
Why am I talking to you
if you gotta call your superiors?
-We don't always see eye-to-eye.
-Yeah, so I'll talk to them.
I'll see what they say.
I talk to them and I ask them,
all right? Then we'll see.
Anything else I can give you?
Yeah, I want you to bring
my wife down here.
-What do you give us?
-What do you want?
The women hostages.
Oh, man. You know,
there's no talking to you.
That's all I got in there,
I told you, is women.
You gonna talk to me or what?
I'll give you one hostage
for each thing you give me, see?
Give me the helicopter,
I give you a hostage.
Give me the jet, I give you a hostage.
You give me my wife,
I give you a hostage.
Then the rest come home on the jet.
I'll see what they'll do, all right?
In the meantime, you pick out
who you wanna give us.
And you tell me where
your wife is, all right?
I'm here minding my own business,
I hear the transistor, go, "Sonny what?"
I can't believe my ears.
I grab the kids.
I'm telling you, Sonny didn't do it.
lt ain't him to rob a bank!
It ain't him to steal or hurt anybody
or do nothing wrong!
He's never done wrong
since the day I know him.
Night before last we're at Coney Island.
I'm looking in the glove compartment.
He's got a gun with bullets in it.
Things are adding up
how crazy he's acting lately...
. . .and in with a bad crowd.
So I look at him.
Go on, get in bed. He's yelling
at the kids like a madman.
Then he wants me to go on a
kiddie ride. I don't wanna go.
He starts screaming at me.
Sweetheart.
He's screaming and screaming.
I say, "What are you
gonna do with the gun?
Shoot me and dump me in the river?"
I mean, I was scared of him.
I never been scared of him.
His mother says we was always fighting,
the cops was always at our house.
I hit him with a jack handle
once in the car.
Only I didn't even hit him,
I hit myself.
You should've seen the bruise
on my leg, from here to here.
He'd put on his hat and coat,
he goes out the door.
So they tell me he did it.
But I don't believe it.
Mrs. Wortzik, please, listen to me.
They want you down at the bank.
His body functions might've done it,
but he himself, he didn't do it!
"Dear Abby: Lately I've been dreaming
about falling into water. . .
. . .and not being able
to reach the surface.
I begin to breathe heavily
and I wake up in a cold sweat.
A friend tells me that my problem
is one of sexual repression."
-Margaret, are you all right?
-No.
What are you, a renegade, a bandit?
What kind of man are you...
. . .siding with the Indians
against his own people?
-What's your grudge against me?
-I'm taking you in for murder, Kilgore.
Yeah?
Are you doing anything
to any of those girls in there?
He's back again.
Well?
Who is this?
Look at Margaret.
What's the matter with her?
There's no air in here.
What happened to the air conditioning?
-I'm sorry, Syl.
-It's all right.
-Where's the air conditioning?
-The basement.
Sal, I'm gonna go
check the air conditioning.
-I'll be right back.
-Sonny.
What?
I never been up in an airplane before.
So? I mean--
I mean, it's safe. It's like a car.
It's safer than a car.
It's all right, Sal.
-I'm gonna go check it now.
-Okay.
-Sal !
-What?
-They're coming in the back!
-In the vault! Come on.
-Goddamn it, move!
-Back, get back.
No, don't shoot!
That's it, Sonny! Get her in there!
Do it!
Get her in there!
Who fired that shot?
Pick her up by the legs.
Who fired the shot?
Come on ! Move!
Okay, legs. I'll bring her.
-They're moving good.
-What's that?
Sonny?
Sonny! Get me a bullhorn.
Sonny!
-You got that bullhorn?
-Right. Here.
Hey, Sonny.
Come on out, Sonny.
-Sonny.
-Sonny!
That's all I need.
-Sonny?
-Sonny!
Come on, take care of that, will you?
-Sonny, come on out.
Go straighten that out,
will you, Carmine? Sonny!
Sonny, come on out.
-Sonny?
-You did fine.
Sonny.
Sonny!
You son of a bitch,
you wanna get those people killed?
Come on out, Sonny.
Sonny, come on out.
Come on out here, now.
Come on out, Sonny. Sonny!
Sonny?
Come on out here, Sonny.
All right, I see it, Sonny. Come on.
Come on. All right, get back.
Wait, wait. People, wait.
Keep going.
What's the matter with you?
-What?
-What're you firing that shot for?
We got 250 cops here!
Fuck you ! What were
they doing back there?
What the hell's the matter with you?
Are we dealing?
-They were trying to get in, right?
-Who?
Come on, don't give me that shit.
You know who.
-What's going on?
-You're full of shit!
Find out what's going on there!
-Honest to God, Sonny, I don't know--
-Bullshit!
Communications aren't set up yet.
-Get someone to talk to me!
-Goddamn it.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
-Let me talk to you.
-You say this, you do that.
Why were they back there?!
-I don't know!
-You're full of shit.
That's another force, a tactical force!
They like to shoot,
climb through windows!
They like that, right?
Without your orders, right?
No. Yes! Without my orders!
-You're not coming through the roof?
-I tell you we won't.
You're telling me a lot of things,
but you're not doing them.
What were they doing?!
-I don't know!
-You can't answer me, right?
-You can't answer me.
-What?
-Yes, I can.
So tell me what they were doing.
No communications!
I sent someone back there.
I got a guy in there who's gonna kill
somebody. That's your responsibility.
-Not mine, that's yours.
-Wait a minute, hold on. Let's--
-We got everything you wanted.
-Oh, yeah?
Yeah. We can't get a helicopter in here,
but a bus is coming.
We got a jet coming into Kennedy,
all right?
Okay? All right?
Now, we got ahold of your wife.
Your wife is coming.
We reached her
and she's coming here, all right?
-Okay?
-Where you going? Where you going?
I'm right here.
I thought we were gonna talk.
I thought so too.
But we're not talking.
We're trying to get in the back door.
Your wife will be here
in about a half-hour. Okay?
They're still pointing.
They love to point.
Holster that weapon !
Holster it!
You too!
All right, come on.
-What?
-What else do you want me to do?
How could you do any better?
We got everything you wanted.
I'll do anything I can
to stop anything I can.
Anything else?
-Yeah.
-What?
I got some people
in there that are hungry.
-Can you get some food?
-No problem. What do you want?
-Want some pizzas?
-Yeah, all right.
Pizzas?
Hey, Carmine, get some food,
some pizzas.
Can we get some beer, you think?
No beer.
Let's keep it to soft drinks, all right?
Come on. All right? Carmine. . .
. . .some soft drinks too, okay?
Cokes.
-What else?
-I need some aspirin too.
Some lady's not feeling well.
You got it. Anything else?
-Just don't fucking con me.
-I'm not. Why would I wanna do that?
I'm in trouble enough as it is.
I'm not trying to create any trouble.
All right?
It's okay.
They can't-- They can't bring
a helicopter in here, Sal.
Because they can't land it here.
But they're gonna get us a limo bus--
A big bus so we can all get in.
And that's how we get to the airport.
It's good. It looks good.
You people,
I just ordered you some food, so. . . .
I even got her some aspirins.
Okay? So we're moving it along now.
I gotta pay for the food.
Where's the marked fives?
That was a foolish thing
you did back there.
Yeah? Foolish thing.
We gonna get the ball rolling?
Yeah, what do you think I'm doing?
I'm working on it, right?
What's it look like?
You think it's easy?
I gotta keep them cool.
I gotta keep all you people happy.
I gotta have all the ideas
and do it all alone.
I'm working on it.
You wanna try it?
Your food is here, Sonny.
You're starting to get on my nerves.
All right. Go on with him there.
You'll be all right. Go right here.
-What do I owe you?
-It's all paid for.
-It's paid for.
-I paid for it.
No, I got it. I got it.
Here. Keep the change.
What?
-You want this?
-Yeah !
You like it?
Moretti, could you use five?
I got a lot for you.
Get back!
Get back, goddamn it! Get back!
Let him go. Let him go.
More! More! More!
Could you open it?
Thank you, man.
See you later.
I'm a fucking star!
-Okay, kick. . .
-Right.
-. . .out, turn.
-Around.
No, just pick her up and hold her.
She'll be okay.
You're getting your kick good. Here.
Kick, out. . . .
This is where it gets stuck.
-Is that it?
-Yeah.
Here.
-Miriam's making a fool of herself.
-Out.
-Anybody got a cigarette?
-Yeah, I do.
Sylvia, you don't smoke.
You don't smoke?
No.
Why--? Why do you wanna start now?
I'm scared to death, that's why.
What, you don't smoke?
-No.
-How come?
-I don't want the cancer.
-Oh, my God.
-Give me the cigarette.
-Go ahead, do what you want.
I just think you ought to
take care of your body.
My body? What for?
The body is the temple of the Lord.
You're serious.
So you rob a bank. . .
. . . but you keep your body pure.
Is that it?
You gonna smoke or what?
Yes.
If I die of cancer,
it'll be half your fault.
-No, it's because you're weak.
-Right, I'm weak.
-One, two, three--
-Where's your bullets?
Mulvaney speaking.
It's Moretti.
Wants to talk to you.
-Yeah.
-Will you guys hold it down back there?
Sonny, they're bringing in your wife.
Step back. Stay back.
-Where's Moretti?
-Probably in the bar.
In the barbershop.
What's that?
We went to Bellevue
where you told us. . .
. . .said he was his wife.
They were married in a church.
Jesus Christ!
Leon.
Leon !
Hey, Leon, over here!
Leon ! Hey, Leon !
-Now move it back.
-Leon, over here!
Leon ! Happy birthday!
-Hey, give us some room, huh?
-Watch his head.
He's a queer?
Sarge. Sarge, he wants you !
Come on, get the shield out of here.
I don't need it now.
Where were you four hours ago,
when I needed it?
He's not gonna shoot.
Yeah, Sonny, what?
What happened? Is he all right?
-He's a little groggy right now, okay?
-No, let me talk to him.
Let me get him on his feet and
call you back. Shut the fucking door.
Stop the noise in here.
I don't wanna hear a fucking sound !
Typewriter!
-Get off the fucking phone!
-Sarge.
Now!
Give me some water, all right?
Leon? Leon.
You all right, Leon? They give you a shot
down at the hospital or something?
Oh, God.
They shot me with, like, unreal !
You gotta get ahold of yourself. . .
. . .so you can talk to him,
see if he'll come out of the bank.
Oh, no.
He's got eight people, and a kid
named Sal. You know him?
-No, not really.
-Says he's gonna shoot these eight people.
I can't help it.
I can't stop him from anything.
Who will he listen to, then?
I can't-- I can't talk to him.
He won't listen to anybody.
He's been--
He's been crazy all summer.
He's tried to kill me since June.
Yeah. Put a gun to my head.
And he cut me with a knife.
-He beat up my friends.
-Did you contact the police?
What good would that do?
It'd just make him mad. They don't
know him. And it wouldn't stop him.
-Somebody's gotta stop him.
-You don't understand. He's crazy.
He's got a wife, children.
He's a wonderful father.
His mother. . .
. . .you should see her. Together with
his father, they're like a car wreck.
It just-- It just rolls off his back.
He sees them.
He pays the rent. Unbelievable.
I was the one who wanted to get
married. He didn't really want it. . .
. . . but he did it.
I don't know why.
Why did you wanna get married?
I thought it would help me.
But it didn't.
I-- I was so confused.
I was doing. . .
. . . insane things.
What sort of things, Leon?
After the wedding. . .
. . . I ran off for 1 0 days
to Atlantic City.
Sonny was frantic.
He knew I'd been drinking. He didn't
know where I was, who I was with.
I couldn't explain the things I did.
So I went to a psychiatrist. . .
. . .who told me. . .
. . .that I was a woman
trapped in a man's body.
So right away Sonny wanted to give me
money for the sex-change operation.
But where was he gonna get it?
$2500?
My God, he was in hock
up to his ears already.
He needed the money
for your operation?
It drove him crazy. He--
He would fly into these rages.
And I got more depressed than ever.
I knew I'd never get my operation.
So I tried to kill myself.
I took about a half a pound of pills.
Blues, reds, yellows, screamers,
uppers, downers, you name it.
And I wound up in a hospital.
And Sonny comes there. . .
. . .and he just looks at me.
And he says:
"Why, Leon?
When things were going so good?"
Don't you think--?
Leon, don't you think
he sort of did it for you?
Yeah, I guess so.
Don't you think you owe it to him
to try to get him out?
I can't talk to him.
You're up to your neck in it, Leon.
You're an accessory.
-No, no. They can't hold me responsible.
-Wait, you could help us a little.
I'm afraid.
Just talk to him for a minute.
How can he hurt you on the phone?
-All you're gonna be is on the phone.
-I can't. I don't know what to. . . .
-Just talk with him on the phone.
-I can't. No.
You think about it, Leon.
Yeah.
-He doesn't wanna talk to you.
-What do you mean, won't talk to me?
-Let me work on it.
-I thought you were doing that.
He don't wanna talk to me.
Police are questioning Leon Shermer,
a 26-year-old admitted homosexual...
. . .who claims to have married
one of the bank robbers last November.
According to sources in the barbershop
where Leon is being held. . .
. . .Leon has reportedly said. . .
...they were married in an
official ceremony by a Father Burke.
Leon's story has been confirmed.
Seven bridesmaids, all male,
Sonny's mother and 70 other guests...
...all members of the gay community,
were present.
We've been able to obtain
a still photograph of Leon in his gown.
Leon has confirmed. . .
...that the gowns for himseIf
and his bridesmaids cost $700.
We have not confirmed the story...
...with the priest. But we are toId
that he was subsequentIy defrocked.
Phone calls have arrived from
various factions of the gay community.
Some in support of Sonny and his
actions, others totally condemning. . .
...the present events
and calling the marriage a farce...
...and, quote, "A case
of sheer exhibitionism." End quote.
Our coverage of the Brooklyn robbery
where two homosexuals hold hostages...
. . .for their demands of
a helicopter, a jet. . . .
Sonny. Sonny, they said,
"Two homosexuals in the bank."
-Right on TV. You hear?
-What difference does it make?
They're gonna say anything they want.
Let them say it.
Well, I'm not a homosexual.
Tell them to get that right.
That's going out on the TV.
Sal, what am I supposed to do? I can't
control what they say on television.
What should I do? I'm doing
everything I can. I can't do that.
I mean, they're--
Look, Sal.
Forget about it. It's just a freak show
to them, anyway. It don't matter.
Whatever they say, it don't matter.
It'll be all right.
What's the matter with you?
You shouldn't let something like that
spoil your fun, you know?
You gotta get fun out of life.
Shit.
Where's the goddamn jet?
They're always screaming overhead,
going somewhere. . .
. . .when you don't need them,
you know?
What are you gonna tell the pilot
when you get on the plane?
You have to know, right?
-Did you know Holland's pretty good?
-Use this.
-Holland?
-They sheltered people during the war.
They're good people.
Where's Holland?
-It's right up. . . .
-It's over there.
She doesn't have a map.
It's got good chocolate.
Come on, get in the vault.
Get in the vault. Come on.
Quickly!
They're waiting for us
to do something, I think.
Sonny.
-Come on out for a second, please.
-It's him, Sonny.
Come on out here.
I wanna talk to you a second.
-Come on, Sonny.
-Sonny.
Sonny.
Come on out, Sonny.
Sonny?
Come on out a minute.
That's it, Sonny.
Hey, Sonny!
Moretti !
What the fuck is going on?
Get the lights back on.
Moretti !
Who are you?
FBI, Sheldon.
Oh, good.
About time. Maybe we can
get this thing started, huh?
Look, get the lights back on. . .
. . .and the air conditioner.
We got no air conditioning.
-No more favors. That's all over, Sonny.
-Favors?
You been doing me favors all night?
I have a jet, limo will be here
in a half hour.
I want the hostages.
No, no, no. Bullshit.
I'd like to work with you on this,
not against you.
The hostages are
what's keeping me alive.
When do I get them?
Didn't they tell you anything?
I'd like to hear it from you.
You get one hostage for the
limousine that you bring me in.
One hos-- One hostage for the jet.
Then I get to the airport.
I go into the plane, check it all out.
And if it's okay,
then they all come out.
-I wanna go inside.
-Why?
-To see if everybody's all right.
-They're all right.
No, I have to see.
You got guts.
Think if we slit their throats,
we're gonna let you out?
I have to see.
I gotta check with my partner.
The FBI, Sal. They're coming in.
Hey, pussycat. There you go.
You'd like to kill me?
Bet you would.
I wouldn't like to kill you.
I will if I have to.
It's your job, right?
The guy who kills me. . .
. . . I hope he does it because he hates
my guts, not because it's his job.
Nobody give your right name.
It's the FBI.
Just wanna make sure all you
young ladies are all right in here.
-Look. . .
-We're all right.
. . .they asked for the jet hours ago.
Now, what are you doing?
That's being set up.
We'll have you out in a couple of hours.
-A couple of hours?
-Why not give them what they want?
They'll get what they want. We
wanna be sure we get what we want.
That's to get you all out of here safe.
You two boys too.
That's close enough.
Tell the TV to stop saying
there's two homosexuals in here.
I will, Sal.
Outside for a minute, Sonny?
You handle yourself well, Sonny.
A lot of men would have choked. We
might have had a death on our hands.
But you handled it. I respect that.
Now, don't you try to take Sal.
We'll handle him.
-Just sit tight and you won't get hurt.
-Wait. What are you talking about?
You just sit quiet.
We'll handle Sal.
You think I'd sell him out, you fuck?
What'd he say?
He was just talking
about arrangements.
I talked to him about the TV, Sal.
It's gonna be all right.
That's all?
Yeah.
Why couldn't he say that in here?
I don't know. He wanted to show me
how the bus is coming in.
What's the matter?
Somebody get a glass of water.
Got a hankie?
They poisoned the pizza.
It's not the pizza.
He's got diabetes.
He had some Coke before.
Don't give him anything. I'll hold it.
What can we do for you,
Mr. Mulvaney? Tell us.
Is there a doctor out here?
We need a doctor in here.
We need a doctor.
-What's wrong?
-The manager, he's diabetic.
He don't look good.
I gotta search you.
Watch out he don't kiss you, doc.
Looking for an antonym.
Okay.
Just him.
Sonny.
I've convinced Leon to talk to you.
He's on the phone now.
He's coming on.
Hello.
Hello?
Hello, Leon?
Hello. Hello, Sonny.
What happened?
How you--? How you doing?
Well, I'm out of the hospital.
Yeah, I know. You know,
I thought you'd never get out.
Hot. I never thought
I'd get out this way, I'll tell you.
Yeah.
So how you doing?
-I'm a little shaky.
-Oh, yeah?
Moretti told me that you were
all drugged up. . .
. . .so I figured that's why you didn't
talk to me. I was wondering why.
It was really terrible, you know?
I mean, you walk in, and right away
they say you're crazy.
And then they start sticking
things in your arm.
I mean, how do they expect you to get
uncrazy if you're asleep all the time?
I'm-- I'm just starting
to come out of it now.
-So. . . .
-So how are you?
I'm fine.
This is something, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know, Leon, you know?
I'm dying here.
I'm dying.
Don't you ever listen to yourself
when you say you're dying?
-Did you ever listen to yourself?
-What are you talking--?
What do you mean, what am I
talking about? You're dying.
Do you know that you say that
to me every day? "I'm dying."
You're not dying.
You're killing the people around you.
Leon, don't give me that shit.
I don't need the deep shit now!
You don't realize what
the things you do mean.
Yeah? I know what I do.
You stick a gun
to somebody's head.
-I don't know what I'm doing sometimes.
-ObviousIy, you don't.
"Go to sleep
so it won't hurt when I shoot."
What do you think
I've been doing in the hospital?
I take a handful of pills
to get away from you.
-Right?
-Yeah.
So now I'm talking to you
on the phone again, right?
I-- I-- I got no job.
I don't have friends.
I can't live.
I have to live with people.
This death business, I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'm getting here
with that shit.
You know, what am I supposed
to say to that shit? This is going on.
-And you're giving me that shit.
-I'm sorry.
You know what's happening with me.
You know the pressures
I've been having, right?
I got all these pressures. You know it.
You're in that hospital. . .
. . .with them tubes coming out
and want that operation, right?
You're giving me that shit.
Everybody's giving me shit.
Everybody needs money.
So you needed money? I got you money.
-I didn't ask you to rob a bank!
-I know you didn't ask me.
Look, I'm not putting this
on anybody, you know?
Nothing on nobody.
I did this on my own. You see?
All on my own, I did it.
But I just want you to know something.
I want you to know
that I'm getting out of here.
I'm getting a plane out of here. . .
. . .and I just wanted you to know it.
And I wanted you to come down. . .
. . .and I wanted to just say
goodbye to you.
Or, if you wanted to,
you can come with me.
You're free to do what you want.
That's just what. . .
...I wanted to say to you, that's all.
-I'm-- I'm free to do what I want, huh?
-Right.
I been trying to get away from you for
months and I'm going with you on a trip?
Where? Where are you going?
I don't know where yet.
We said Algeria. I don't know.
So I'll go to Algeria.
I don't know yet.
Why are you going to Algeria?
I don't know why. They got
a Howard Johnson's there.
Howard Johnson's. You're warped, you
know? You're really warped.
I'm warped. I know I'm warped.
God, Algeria. It's--
You know, they walk around
with masks on, things on their heads.
-They're a bunch of crazy people.
-What am I supposed to do?
-You could have picked a better place.
-Like where?
Sweden? Denmark?
Yeah, I like that. Yeah.
You know what?
Sal wanted to go to Wyoming.
I had to tell him it's not a country.
He don't know where Wyoming is.
I'm with a guy who don't know where
Wyoming is. Think you got problems?
So, Sal is with you?
Oh, boy.
You'd be better off giving up.
I'm not giving up, because
why have I done this so far?
I've gone so far with this,
and why should I give up now?
I can't give up.
-Would you do me a favor then?
-Yeah, what?
These guys that have me
down here, you know. . .
. . .they think I'm part of the plot
to rob the bank.
That's crazy, Leon. That's crazy.
They're bullshitting you,
giving you a snow job.
-They told me I was an accessory.
-No.
That's just a con job on you.
Don't listen to that.
I have to listen to it.
I can't survive in prison, Sonny.
-Leon, you're not going to prison.
-How do you know?
Because I know. Believe me.
-Look, please, just tell them.
-Please what?
Tell them what?
That you didn't do it?
Are they on the phone now?
-Are they on the phone now?
-Yeah.
That's great, Leon.
That's really terrific.
You talk to me with them on the phone.
Really smart.
-I have no choice!
-What do you mean?
What am I supposed to do? There's
7000 fucking cops all around me.
-Who's on now?
-Look, don't Iay it on me!
I'm not, but you knew
that was going on, right?
You knew what was happening, right?
Yeah !
I wanna know
who's on the phone now.
Moretti. Moretti, is that you?
Hello.
Will somebody talk to me?
Somebody gonna talk to me or what?
-They on the phone now?
-They won't talk to you.
All right. He didn't do it, okay?
He had nothing to do with it.
All right. Now, will you get
the fuck off the phone?
Are they off the phone?
Yeah.
Terrific. That really convinced them.
That's what they wanted to know.
-Did I do it for you?
-Yeah, thank--
-Thank you very much.
-Okay.
So now what?
What are you gonna do?
Well, I thought. . .
. . .that I would
go back to the hospital.
They're really nice there. They
seem like they're trying to help me.
That's good, then.
You found something.
Yeah, I don't know if I have or not.
So are you gonna still
have the operation?
Yeah. Yeah.
So then, what am I
supposed to say to you?
Thanks a lot. . .
. . .and bon voyage.
Yeah, right.
See you sometime.
Yeah. I'll see you in my dreams, huh?
Right, I'll write a song.
-I don't know. Life's so funny.
-You said a mouthful, sweetheart.
Well-- Goodbye, huh?
Bye.
-Yeah.
-Give me-- Can I have--?
-Moretti. Moretti.
-Hey. Hey.
You cut off the incoming calls.
Can I have a line?
I wanna talk to my wife
and to my kids.
He wants an outside line,
is it all right?
-I want a line.
-Yeah, Sonny, I'm getting it.
I could call anybody,
they'd put them on the phone.
The Pope, an astronaut. . .
. . .the wisest of the wise.
Who do I have to call?
I just don't know what to do.
-Hello.
-Angie.
Sonny, Jesus!
I was watching it on TV.
-Yeah. So where are the kids?
-I sent them to the neighbors.
I can't believe. I can't believe.
I mean, it ain't like you.
I know.
You've never done anything
like it before in your life.
I'm dying, you know that?
I'm dying here.
I blame myself. I notice you been
tense, like something is happening.
Like that night you're yelling
at the kids like a madman.
Then you want me to go...
. . .on that ride, here
to there, full of those kids.
It's ridiculous. I'm not about to go,
so you yell at me:
"You pig, get on the fucking ride!"
Everything fell out of me.
My heart, my liver just fell to the floor.
I mean, everything.
You know what it felt like? You yelling
at me in front of all those people?
You never talked to me
like that before, Sonny.
I think, "He's gonna shoot me,
dump my body in the river."
-WiII you just shut up?
-I was scared of you !
Will you shut the fuck up and
listen to me?! Just listen to me!
You see that?
With the language and everything.
I'm trying to talk to you, and you--
A person can't communicate with you !
I mean, what am I here?
I'm your wife. I'm your wife!
You know something?
You hurt me.
You hurt me, you know that?
Can you imagine, marrying another man?
Did I ever do anything
to make you do that?
Did I ever turn you down or anything?
I know I let myself get fat.
-Don't call yourself fat.
-You can't stand me to say it.
Like I can't stand you being
a bank robber. That's what love is.
Yeah? You know what love is, right?
If you know what love is so much,
why didn't you come down here?
-Well. . . .
-Talk to me about love, go ahead.
Sonny, I'm scared.
I'm scared. Are they
gonna shoot me or something?
They're not gonna shoot you !
You should see it on the TV.
They got cannons, machine guns.
They're after me, Angie, not you.
It's late already
by the time I find out. . .
...it's just you and Sal. I can't
get a babysitter! What'll I do?
Listen, I think I better take him back
for a cardiac check.
So, what's the matter?
What, he gonna die or what?
No, no. It's just a precautionary
measure. It's awfully warm in here.
All right, then. Let's go,
let him out.
I'm not going. I'm okay.
I just needed the injection.
What, you trying to be a hero?
You don't look good. We'll let you out.
I'm not trying to be anything.
I just wanna be left alone.
Okay?
-No one's bothering you.
-I wish to fuck you never came.
That's all.
Don't try to act like
you're some angel of human kindness.
Out of the closets and into the streets!
Sonny all the way!
Ladies.
I wanna apologize
for my use of language back there.
Why? What did you say,
Mr. Mulvaney?
-What did he say?
-He said the F-word.
-What?
-What did he say?
He said the F-word.
-Fuck.
-I know, Miriam.
Fuck.
But I'm a Christian
and my ears are not garbage cans.
Come on.
Oh, Edna.
-Then we shouldn't go after them.
-Then we won't.
-What's that?
-Sonny.
Could you come out, please?
Sonny?
-Shit.
-What?
-It's my mother.
-Sonny.
Someone here to see you. Sonny. . .
-. . .could you come out, please?
-Oh, who needs this shit?
Sonny. Sonny,
could you come out, please?
Mom, what are you doing down here?
-I don't need you down here.
-Oh, Sonny.
All of Brooklyn is out here.
Three networks of television.
-I got it all worked out, Ma.
-I talked to the man from the FBI.
Who?
No, don't talk to anybody.
He says if you come out now,
everything is gonna be all right.
-I'm trying to get you out of this.
-Don't talk to the FBI.
I told them everything. . .
. . . how you were in the war in Vietnam,
I told them you always had good jobs.
I told them you were with Goldwater
in '64 in the convention and--
Listen, I'm getting a plane
and I'm going to Algeria.
-I'll write you from there.
-Algeria?
-I gotta get out of here.
-I don't understand.
If I stay and talk to you,
they won't send the limousine.
-They'll think I'll come out with you.
-What's the matter with that?
Because I'm not coming with you.
The FBI understands everything,
that it is not you that is doing this.
It's the pressures from your home life!
-Don't get on Angie now.
-Did I say one word against her?
You were going to. She has
nothing to do with it, it's me!
Your life was sweetness and roses.
And you--
You wouldn't need Leon if Angie
was treating you right, you know that!
I don't understand why you
wanna sleep with her anyway.
You got two kids on welfare now.
-You want three kids on welfare?
-I can't talk to you about this now.
What are you gonna do?
All right, come out.
I can't come out. I can't.
Sal is in there with the people.
-If I come out, he's gonna kill them.
-Oh, my God.
Run. Run.
Run? Where am I gonna run?
Ma, I can't run.
-Maybe--
-There's no maybe. No maybes.
You gotta go home. Where's Pop?
He didn't come, did he?
Is he pissed off at you !
He says he doesn't have a son.
-He says you're dead.
-He's right.
-No. No.
-Look, Ma. . .
. . . I'm a fuck-up and an outcast
and that's it.
You come near me, you're
gonna get fucked over and fucked out!
Now, I gotta go, Ma.
Get her home, okay?
Just take her home.
How beautiful you were
when you were a baby.
Go home now. Get her home now.
All right.
Ten minutes.
Being of sound mind. . .
. . .and body. . . .
You know, what they. . . .
To my darling wife. . .
. . . Leon. . .
. . .whom I love. . .
. . . more than any man. . .
. . . has loved another man. . .
. . . in all eternity.
I leave. . .
. . .$2700. . .
. . .from my $1 0,000
life-insurance policy. . .
. . .to be used. . .
. . .for your sex-change operation.
If there is any money left over. . .
. . . I want it to go to you. . .
. . .at my first--
At the first anniversary
of my death. . .
. . .at my grave.
To my wife. . .
. . .to my sweet wife. . .
. . .Angela. . .
. . .$5000 from the same policy.
You are the only woman. . .
. . .that I ever loved.
And I repledge my love to you. . .
. . . in this sad moment.
To little Kimmy. . .
. . .and Timmy.
I hope you remember me, Timmy.
You are the little man
of the family now. . .
. . .and I hope
you look after them for me.
To my mother. . .
. . . I ask forgiveness.
You-- You don't understand. . .
. . .the things I said. . .
. . .and did.
But I'm me and I'm different.
I want a military funeral. . .
. . .and I'm entitled to have one,
free of charge.
God-- God bless you. . .
. . .and watch over you. . .
. . .till we are joined in the hereafter.
Here, I'll sign.
I'll spell that last name.
-Watch out!
-Watch out over here.
Look out over here. Watch it.
Come on, sarge, just one picture?
Back, back!
All you guys, back up!
-You're the driver?
-Yeah.
All right. I wanna check it out.
-These seats come out?
-No, they're bolted.
All right, here.
Light me on that side.
Give me light over there.
All right.
Jesus, you're the man, huh?
I was watching. I saw you, man.
You should see yourself,
you wouldn't believe it.
-I believe it.
-Goddamn, Sheila won't believe it.
-Who's Sheila?
-My old lady.
They said, "Gas up a stretch. . .
-. . .go to 285 Prospect Park West."
-Give me some light over here.
I said, "Shit, another load
for the massage parlors."
It's okay.
My man, I'm gonna remember you.
This is Agent Murphy.
He'll be your driver.
No, I want him.
-Give me the black guy.
-Hey, man, I ain't into that shit.
Nobody'll hurt you.
If they would've shot,
they would've shot already.
-I can't allow that, Sonny.
-You can't allow?
What makes you think you can
say shit to me? I'm running this.
I'll pay you. What do you want?
A hundred? Two hundred?
A thousand? Come on.
Don't look at him, I'm running this.
Come on.
Look, it'll be an adventure.
You men that shoot,
aim for white meat.
Take a walk.
Give me him.
You think you're dealing
with a fucking idiot?
Take a walk, cop!
Everybody is a con man. Come on.
I want everyone across the street.
I want them all back,
on the sidewalk!
Let's go!
At least I know
who I'm dealing with now.
Here's a pen for you. Come on.
Don't move, okay?
Sonny, here's your document.
-Right.
-Oh, you gotta sign it. Here.
We're taking off. We're going now.
Okay, Sal. Where is he? Sal?
Sal.
That's it, we're going.
Here, people, let's go. We're going.
-Can I get my sweater?
-Get what you had when you came in.
Sal?
Sal.
-How you doing?
-Good.
-Good? We're gonna do it, right?
-Yeah.
We're gonna do it. Sal, see. . .
. . .you gotta keep your eye on him.
He's the driver.
-I need it.
-No, it's mine.
You gotta keep
your eye on him, Sal, see?
All right, where am I now?
All right, hold it. Hold it.
All right, let's go.
Swing around now. Swing around.
Just keep holding hands.
Hold it.
Break it on "three."
Not yet, don't break yet.
One. . .
. . .two. . .
-. . .three. Go.
-Go.
Oh, fuck. We did it.
-We did it.
-Wish us luck.
Bye-bye.
-Okay, you got your one.
-Follow my car.
Sheldon here, get me Kennedy.
-Sal, we did it.
-Yeah.
I'll be a son of a bitch, we did it.
Okay, let's move.
Come on, honk the horn.
Hey, Sal, do me a favor, will you?
Keep the gun pointed up.
We hit a bump, the gun'll go off.
All right. You set out there?
We're leaving now.
We want no trouble en route.
-Intersection check?
-Check.
-All right. We'll be starting up right now.
-10-4.
It's gonna be all right.
Sal.
Sal, you just gotta remember
to keep the gun pointed up.
You fucking--
Hey, let him go!
What's he doing?
He's still got some
arrangements to make.
-That's it?
-That's it.
Sal, see it? There it is.
Oh, I forgot.
I forgot to ask if they
got food on board.
They gonna have food on board?
There's your jet. We get one more now.
That's the deal.
Right. Okay, who goes?
Sylvia?
Maria.
I'll pray for you.
Sal. . .
. . . because this is
your first plane trip. . .
. . .don't be scared, okay?
I didn't eat all day.
Will there be any food on board?
There'll be hamburgers. Ready?
-Sal.
-What?
Ready to go?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's move it.
Sal. . .
. . .we don't want any accidents
at this point, right?
You keep your gun pointed up.
You ready to get out first?
I'm ready.
Don't shoot me.
Wait, hold it. Hold it. Hold it.
Hold it, please.
Okay, it's safe. Come on.
Put him away, put him away.
All right, guys, move back.
Come on, back up.
Now spread them !
No. No, we're all secure here.
Murphy will report from the car.
You make the report.
Put the gun down.
Back off.
Get up now, Sonny.
You're under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney
during your interrogation.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
If you cannot afford to hire a lawyer. . .
. . .one will be appointed
to represent you if you wish one.
Agent Sheldon, would you please
remain on the apron...
...until the hostages are
well inside the terminal?
Repeat:
Agent Sheldon, would you please
remain on the apron...
...until the hostages are
well inside the terminal?
Yeah, I got you.
We'll hold here.